{
  "items": [
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'What is your favorite holiday?' Tom said 'one where I get to meet lots of different people.' Jerry said 'What was the most number of people you have ever met during a holiday?' Tom said 'Hard to keep a count. Maybe 25.' Jerry said 'Which holiday was that?' Tom said 'I think it was Australia.' Jerry said 'Do you still talk to the people you met?' Tom said 'Not really. The interactions are usually short-lived but it's fascinating to learn where people are coming from and what matters to them.' Jerry said 'Yea, me too. I feel like God often puts strangers in front of you, and gives you an opportunity to connect with them in that moment in deeply meaningful ways. Do you ever feel like you know things about strangers without them telling you?' Tom said 'what do you mean?' Jerry said 'I think it's like a 6th sense, often seen as \"cold readings\" to people, but can be remarkably accurate. I once sat next to a man in a coffee and I felt a pain in my back. I asked the stranger if he had a pain. It turns out that he did in the exact spot, and said he pulled a muscle while dancing at a party. I had never met the man before and never saw him again.' Tom said 'Wow! That's interesting, borderline spooky.' Jerry said 'There's this practice called \"Treasure Hunting\" that's kind of a fun game you play in a public place. There's a book called \"The Ultimate Treasure Hunt\" that talks about it. You use your creativity to imagine people you will meet, and you write down a description, then you associate them with a positive message or encouraging word. Maybe you saw a teenage boy in a red hat at the shopping mall in your imagination, then while at the mall, you may find someone who matches that description. You show that you have a message for him and that you have a message for a boy in a red hat. You then give him a message of kindness or whatever was on your heart. You have no idea, sometimes you meet someone who is having a really hard day, and it brings them to tears to have a stranger show them love.'",
      "question": "What was the most number of people Tom has met during a holiday?",
      "answer": "25"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi.' Jerry said 'Any plans for the weekend?' Tom said 'my friends are gonna visit me this weekend. we might go hiking!' Jerry said 'That's great! How's the weather over the weekend? I hope its warm.' Tom said 'Should be very sunny! you?' Jerry said 'Cool! very depressing plans ... stay home and work üòû I have a project deadline very close.' Tom said 'üòê hope you get your work done very soon! a bug free weekend!' Jerry said 'Right, very anxious! where do you plan to go for a hike?' Tom said 'I am going to Diablo!' Jerry said 'Nice, where is that place? I haven't been there.' Tom said 'hours drive from here. still in bay area.' Jerry said 'That's cool! How long is the hike?' Tom said 'Actually no idea, but it will take the entire day for that.' Jerry said 'nice! sounds fun!'",
      "question": "Where does Tom plan to go for a hike?",
      "answer": "Diablo"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey there! What's up???' Tom said 'Nothing much, how you doin?' Jerry said 'I'm in New York this week for Thanksgiving. I'm squatting in the office today and I caught up with an old friend of mine :D.' Tom said 'Oh wow! Sounds like fun! When was the last time you had seen this friend?' Jerry said 'The last time in New York, back in June.' Tom said 'Ohh okay. I was going to say if it had been a long time maybe it'd be awkward...' Jerry said 'Haha, I guess if it's been a very long time there's almost too many life events to catch up on.. especially recently.' Tom said 'Oh really? Has a lot changed in your life recently?' Jerry said 'Haha it's probably too much to go into at the moment. Let's just say life is an exciting experience. How about you?' Tom said 'Ahhh sounds exciting indeed! My life is pretty bland. I like routine, but sometimes I wish I had more time for adventures!' Jerry said 'What kinds of adventures?? Any ones that I would be able to join you on?' Tom said 'Hmmmm. I really want to try bull riding. Do you have any interest in that?' Jerry said 'I'd love to try! Can we schedule something for next week?' Tom said 'Sure! What does your Saturday look like?' Jerry said 'Saturday looks pretty good, shall we shoot for something in the morning?'",
      "question": "When was the last time Jerry saw his old friend?",
      "answer": "June"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hey.' Tom said 'is it raining pretty bad today?' Jerry said 'yeah, can walk too far to see all the foodtruck options.' Tom said 'surprising that the rain started early this year... I don't like them too much. They make days gloomy.' Jerry said 'yeah but I think it's good to have some rainy days in bay area, it's pretty dry here üòõ' Tom said 'Where I grew up, we had lots of water trouble too...' Jerry said 'yeah like wise, I've seen a pretty bad snowstorm when I was at my undergrad school, all flights canceled and traffics went down.' Tom said 'Haha... I don't think I can survive in that weather ever. Just the rains at 50 degrees make me want to sit in heated rroms.' Jerry said 'yeah how do you like it in bay area though? I think we need more rain here.' Tom said 'people say there is drought here... but we have 24 hours water supply here ... lol... never seen that in a drought ridden area.' Jerry said 'it is pretty dry in the mountains I believe, that's what causes fire.' Tom said 'hmm.... okay. Climate change talk this morning was pretty darn interesting. did you see it?' Jerry said 'nope, what does it say?' Tom said 'they were talking about how AI is helping climate change. Nice use of upcoming tech.'",
      "question": "What does Tom think about rain?",
      "answer": "Gloomy"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi.' Jerry said 'Helloooooo!' Tom said 'How are you? How is your day?' Jerry said 'Good. Don't have much to do today, feels good. How are you?' Tom said 'I'm dressed very wel today so I feel good! I've been reading a lot about the psychology of positive outlook.' Jerry said 'So what's your outlook? Something blue?' Tom said 'Yes. Blue is a tranquil colour. It's a good metaphor. Do you have good advice for positivity?' Jerry said 'You should drink more water, do some push up, and sleep early.'",
      "question": "What color does Tom associate with tranquility?",
      "answer": "Blue"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, how are you?' Tom said 'I'm a bit sad. I miss my cat.' Jerry said 'Oh no‚Ä¶ Have you sent out the missing cat posters? Hope your cat is alright!' Tom said 'Posters is a great idea. So far I've just tried banging her catfood dish and shouting her name. Anyway, how is your day going so far?' Jerry said 'Yea, I know they love the plastic bag sound all the time. I am good, nothing special though.' Tom said 'If you could go anywhere on vacation, where would you go?' Jerry said 'I like rainforest, but I know it requires extensive training beforehand.' Tom said 'I heard there are rainforests in southeast Asia where you can zipline from tree to tree.' Jerry said 'I am afraid I will be scared of doing this :)' Tom said 'I won't lie, it sounds scary. I'm scared right now just thinking about it.' Jerry said 'I don't know if there is any medication for acrophobia. I want to take plenty of it if I really have to do it.' Tom said 'If there isn't one, you should invent it, and then make millions.' Jerry said 'That's a great idea! Maybe alcohol is such a thing.' Tom said 'Ha! Don't drink and zipline, mate!' Jerry said 'Oops. I won't do it again. Ha.'",
      "question": "What has Tom done to try and find his missing cat?",
      "answer": "Banged dish"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey sup.' Tom said 'not much. any plans this weekend?' Jerry said 'I'm going to try that thing where you hang from a wire as you go down. do you know what is it called?' Tom said 'ziplining?' Jerry said 'that's the one! have you ever tried it?' Tom said 'i have a couple years ago. it's quite a unique experience.' Jerry said 'where did you do it?' Tom said 'i forgot where it was, it wasn't local i don't think though.' Jerry said 'no worries. what's the most exciting thing you ever done?' Tom said 'that's a hard question and i'm tired so i'm going to go. see you.' Jerry said 'sure. are you just going home now?' Tom said 'no, i'm going to get a massage first.' Jerry said 'nice. what type?' Tom said 'traditional kind.' Jerry said 'yeah I want to get one too soon.' Tom said 'you should! it's relaxing after a long day. talk to you later!' Jerry said 'ttyl!'",
      "question": "What type of massage is Tom getting?",
      "answer": "Traditional"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello, have you seen any good movies lately?' Tom said 'I watched a few lately, but nothing is as good as Avatar. what's your favorite?' Jerry said 'I have never seen Avatar, what is it about? I really enjoy the Avenger movies.' Tom said 'it's a science-fiction movie with beautiful landscape of an imaginary nature with non-human creatures. people figured out a way to join that nature through Avatar transformation. the movie ends with a meaningful story of how human behaviors, e.g., cutting trees, have affected nature.' Jerry said 'That sounds really cool! I think that movie did really well when it was in the box office so it must be good!' Tom said 'yea. what else do you like to do beside movies?' Jerry said 'I enjoy baking cookies. I am on a quest to bake the best chocolate chip cookie üôÇ What about you?' Tom said 'I enjoy eating üôÇ' Jerry said 'so definitely would like to try your best chocolate cookie.' Tom said 'I will have to bake some soon and let you know. What types of food do you like to eat?' Jerry said 'thanks! I generally love noodle soups like Pho or Ramen :)' Tom said 'Noodle soup is delicious! Do you make homemade noodle soup or do you prefer to go out?' Jerry said 'I prefer to go out. I'm not a good cook haha.' Tom said 'Same! Even though I bake, I cannot cook.' Jerry said 'seems like we share a thing in common, yay!'",
      "question": "What type of food does Jerry generally love?",
      "answer": "Noodle soups"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Good afternoon!' Tom said 'How has your week been?' Jerry said 'So far so good. It is holiday season. So just chilling.' Tom said 'I think I'm getting sick with a cold üòû So you should chill on my behalf too cause I'm out the game for all of December.' Jerry said 'lol Sorry to hear that. Are you planning anything fun for December?' Tom said 'Nothing exciting. I'll be posted up at home for the most part. I did a lot of travelling this year so my budget would have stopped me even if I wasn't sick.' Jerry said 'üòÇ' Tom said 'Do you have big plans?' Jerry said 'Yes! I am going to Hawaii! This will be my first time visiting Hawaii. Really excited about it.' Tom said 'I love Hawaii. It's a good place to be. I like going there cause it's humid so I never have to put on lotion.' Jerry said 'lol this is the first time I heard from a boy who cares about humidity and lotion. I cannot agree more.' Tom said 'Brooooo!!! It's so important. When I got to California beaches I have to carry 3 litres of lotion for the whole day.' Jerry said 'üòÇ'",
      "question": "Where is Jerry planning to travel in December?",
      "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Oh hello. Long time no talk. How's the day going for yuo?' Tom said 'Very well, thanks for asking. How has your day been?' Jerry said 'Getting better. I just recovered from a cold. I got wet in the rain last week. Are you planning anything for the holidays?' Tom said 'Glad to hear you're better. Sorry to hear you were sick. I was sick a couple of weeks ago with a bad cough. There's definitely a bug going around. Admit I just want to stay healthy for the holidays and plan to relax.' Jerry said 'Oh same here. I think relaxing at home should be counted among the best ways to enjoy the holidays.' Tom said 'Definitely! I know a lot of folks travel for the holidays, but I'm happy to stay home myself!' Jerry said 'I'm getting there. Every year until last year, I tried to go somewhere for the Christmas / New Year, and then I got bored traveling. lol not sure if that means I'm getting old?' Tom said 'Me too. Now I have folks come visit me for the holidays! But that's also tiresome..' Jerry said 'Are you doing any home decorating then?' Tom said 'Yes! We set up an eco-friendly (i.e. fake) Christmas tree and put up some colorful LED lights which is very festive.' Jerry said 'I think I'm copying you. Me and my wife plan to decorate and Christmas tree too. We bought most of the decorative stuffs from the stores, but haven't yet to buy the tree.' Tom said 'Buying a tree is a neat experience. I was torn between buying an artificial/eco-friendly/fake one vs. a real one that smells like fresh pine. In the end, we opted for the one that we can disassemble every year.' Jerry said 'I see. Artificial anything is better, from tree to intelligence, huh?'",
      "question": "What type of Christmas tree did Tom choose?",
      "answer": "Artificial"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey.' Tom said 'How's your day going?' Jerry said 'pretty good. yours?' Tom said 'Ehh it's fine. I didn't do so well on that history test, actually..' Jerry said 'oh what happened?' Tom said 'Apparently Christopher Columbus didn't fight in the Civil War :')' Jerry said 'hahah wait for real?' Tom said 'I know right! Are you taking History next semester?' Jerry said 'No I'm not in school anymore.' Tom said 'Oh I see. What do you do?' Jerry said 'I train and compete in horse vaulting.' Tom said 'Oh wow. Were you born a horse, or were you turned into one?' Jerry said 'lol you're too funny.' Tom said 'Just kidding. That sounds pretty cool! Is it your job?' Jerry said 'Yeah, but I part time work on a farm. Helping with a bit of everything.' Tom said 'Wow, sounds very busy! Do you with money at those horse vaulting competitions?' Jerry said 'Yeah some. enough to get by.'",
      "question": "What does Jerry do for work?",
      "answer": "Horse vaulting"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello.' Tom said 'Do you have a favourite flower?' Jerry said 'hmm, I haven't thought about that much, but i think lotus should be one of my favorites. Why do you ask?' Tom said 'I'm working on a theory. Why does the lotus spring to mind?' Jerry said 'Nice! Lotus looks pretty cool and It has some delightful vibe. So what is this research about?' Tom said 'Oh, it's not research! Just a personal theory. I think that flower preferences are more revealing of personality than people appreciate.' Jerry said 'Interesting! Whats your favorite flower?' Tom said 'The gerbera. It's like a cartoon flower. As if you drew \"flower\" with a crayon and then it came to life.' Jerry said 'Nice, i would love know more about your theory. Like how you can deduce personality from flower preference.' Tom said 'Ok, step 1 is, you ask someone what their favourite flower is. Pretty much like what we just did. Does that make sense so far?' Jerry said 'yes.' Tom said 'Cool. Step 2: talk with the person some more, and ask them some more questions, and gradually develop a sense of what they're like, over the course of maybe two to five years. And voila.' Jerry said 'Hehe, i think you should publish this someday :)' Tom said 'Why thank you, that's a wonderful idea!'",
      "question": "What is Jerry‚Äôs favorite flower?",
      "answer": "Lotus"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey how's it going.' Tom said 'It's good it's good. How are you?' Jerry said 'good. it's really hot today. I think I'm going to the pool.' Tom said 'Oh nice! Where do you live?' Jerry said 'I live in Tokyo, Japan.' Tom said 'Ahh yes, Japan is hot during the summer. Last time I was in Kyoto it was 114 degrees....' Jerry said 'oh have you been?' Tom said 'Yes yes. I've been to Tokyo as well. It's so nice!' Jerry said 'what did you do here?' Tom said 'Oh everything! I went to an onsen, the fish market, disney land and giant robot fighting show haha.' Jerry said 'lol why did you come to Japan just to go to Disney land?' Tom said 'The Disney lands are all different! There's also Disney Sea, which is completely unique!' Jerry said 'oh neat. I haven't heard about that robot fighting show. where is that??' Tom said 'I don't really remember what part of town it was in. It was pretty cool though - I'm sure you can find it if you google \"giant robot fighting show tokyo\" haha.' Jerry said 'lol ok.'",
      "question": "Where does Jerry live?",
      "answer": "Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Have you seen any good movies lately?' Tom said 'Last weekend I saw \"The Parasite.\" Ever heard of it?' Jerry said 'No. Why did you pick that movie?' Tom said 'My friend wanted to see it. It has great reviews on IMDB and Rotten Tomatoes! What did you do last weekend?' Jerry said 'I played music and worked on some side projects. I also started watching the new Disney service.' Tom said 'Oooo the Mandalorian?!?!' Jerry said 'Mostly, the deleted scenes from Avengers.. lol.' Tom said 'lol Are you a big Marvel fan?' Jerry said 'I loved the X-Men as a kid, and even collected the comic cards. Recently, I got very into the Marvel Cinematic Universe movies. How many Avengers movies have you seen?' Tom said 'I've only seen Spiderman. Honestly it was a little too scary and so I don't think I can bring myself to watch the other Marvel movies! haha.' Jerry said 'Oh!-- I have a friend who looks like the actor who plays Spiderman.' Tom said 'Oh really? To be honest I think the actor is not that good looking, so not so surprising! haha.' Jerry said 'Yea. I think Loki is the most handsome üòÄ' Tom said 'Who is Loki? I've never heard that name before.' Jerry said 'He's the adopted brother of Thor, God of thunder, and is burdened with glorious purpose. Do you feel that burden?'",
      "question": "What movie did Tom watch last weekend?",
      "answer": "The Parasite"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, what's up?' Tom said 'Just chillin'. how are you?' Jerry said 'I'm pretty good, thanks.' Tom said 'Do anything interesting today?' Jerry said 'I went to the local cafe and had a double espresso. It was delicious. What about you?' Tom said 'Oh that's cool! I actually went to an amusement park and went on my first roller coaster!' Jerry said 'Oh my gosh. What was it like??' Tom said 'It was scary! It was actually Kingda Ka, the world's tallest roller coaster. Ever heard of it?' Jerry said 'No, never heard of it. But I'm not really a coaster aficianado. I've heard that some people get addicted to them and travel the world to try them.' Tom said 'Oh wow! I'm not on that level yet, but I understand the appeal. Are you an adrenaline junkie at all?' Jerry said 'No, the opposite. I can't stand heights, horror movies, or confined spaces.' Tom said 'Same! I guess the roller coaster wasn't so bad because I trust the engineering haha.' Jerry said 'Ha, I suppose that makes sense! Would you say that you enjoyed it?' Tom said 'Maybe not so much at the time, but I am glad I did it now that it's done, know what I mean?' Jerry said 'I think I sort of understand :)'",
      "question": "What did Jerry have at the local cafe?",
      "answer": "Double espresso"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hello there, how is it going?' Tom said 'All good. Planning to head home soon. How about you?' Jerry said 'I'm quite tired. There are a lot of things I need to finish before the end of the year.' Tom said 'oh... sorry to hear that. But after that it will be a hard earned vacation.' Jerry said 'yeah, looking forward to it. Hope I don't get pinged during the holidays. Are you going to travel these dates?' Tom said 'I have some tentative plans, but if that doesn't pan out, will just chill at home.' Jerry said 'staying at home is always nice during the holidays.' Tom said 'Where are you based out of these days?' Jerry said 'I'm working from LA, nice weather around here. and you?' Tom said 'San Francisco. It's been raining cats and dogs here since last 2-3 weeks.' Jerry said 'aw man, I'm sorry to hear that. at least it's not snow!' Tom said 'The flu has been hitting hard as well. I had several folks in the house down at one point.' Jerry said 'that's really sad. are they feeling any better?' Tom said 'Yes, everyone recovered now.'",
      "question": "Where is Jerry currently based?",
      "answer": "LA"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello.' Tom said 'How's it going?' Jerry said 'Extremely busy. I have been trying to prepare for the upcoming holidays. How about you?' Tom said 'I'm going to the bahamas. Can't wait!!!' Jerry said 'I'm jealous, take me with you!! I would love to have some warm weather right now.' Tom said 'oh where are you now?' Jerry said 'Canada. There is another major snowstorm that might hit this weekend so I have been rushing to get everything done before it comes.' Tom said 'oh no. I never seen this in person. Is it scary?' Jerry said 'Snow is not scary as long as you're prepared. You just need to be ready to not have electricity for a while. I enjoy the aftermath of a good snowstorm because then you can go sledding or skiing.' Tom said 'that does sound nice. so what are you doing these holidays?' Jerry said 'I am having all of the extended family over for a big meal. We will also go <REDACTED_TERM> as well. What will you do in the bahamas?' Tom said 'nice nice. I'm gonna go snorkeling yey.' Jerry said 'Sounds fun! I wish I knew how to swim!' Tom said 'You can stay on the shallow side I think. Well hope you enjoy time with your extended family!' Jerry said 'That's true. You too, have a great time snorkeling!'",
      "question": "Where is Tom going for the holidays?",
      "answer": "Bahamas"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi! How was your weekend?' Tom said 'pretty good. just went to church and hangout with friends.' Jerry said 'Nice.' Tom said 'did you do anything?' Jerry said 'I made donuts and samosas with an air fryer have you used one of those before.' Tom said 'yum yum yum no only good old oily frier.' Jerry said 'haha.' Tom said 'do you have one at your home or were you at a friends place?' Jerry said 'I was at my parents' place what are you up to for Thanksgiving?' Tom said 'I'm going to impersonate a pumpkin.' Jerry said 'wow, those are unique plans.' Tom said 'I'm pretty unique person.' Jerry said 'I think so too.' Tom said 'any other hobbies besides air frying everything? üôÇ' Jerry said 'I want to start fermenting things kimchi for example sounds like a fun thing to ferment takes a few days apparently miso takes a couple years to fermen.'",
      "question": "What did Jerry make with an air fryer?",
      "answer": "Donuts and samosas"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'heya, nice to meet you, I'm Paul.' Tom said 'nice to meet you too! I'm James. how are you doing today?' Jerry said 'I'm doing OK. Looking forwards to the weekend. how about you?' Tom said 'same here! I hope the weather will be nice.' Jerry said 'oh yeah, but I don't have my hopes too high, I heard there could be a storm coming our way.' Tom said 'oh no, which areas will be affected?' Jerry said 'they mentioned that the whole city will experience harsh weather and that people in the outskirts will probably not get much rain and wind.' Tom said 'uh oh, I'd better not to plan for BBQ then instead just enjoying playing board games inside üôÇ' Jerry said 'yeah, it'll be good weather for staying inside with a cup of hot chocolate. Too bad my street usually floods, so I'll have to check for that.' Tom said 'yea, you'd better check. where do you live?' Jerry said 'I live at the bottom of the valley, cheap area but we do get affected by this kind of stuff a lot haha.' Tom said 'gotcha. anything you love about where you live?' Jerry said 'well, the food around the area is amazing, which is definitely a plus.' Tom said 'nice! I'd love to come visit that area some times.'",
      "question": "Where does Jerry live?",
      "answer": "Bottom of the valley"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hello, who am I having the pleasure to chat with üôÇ' Tom said 'I am the superman! What about you?' Jerry said 'haha. great chating with superman, what is your power?' Tom said 'Being invisible. You won't see me.' Jerry said 'haha. what else can you do? can you read minds?' Tom said 'I would rather trust fMRI and machine learning to do this. I am not an expert on that. Sorry for it!' Jerry said 'wow that seems pretty technical. what does fMRI mean?' Tom said 'The brain imaging thing that can tell you a brain's activity at a pretty high resolution.' Jerry said 'okay! so you seem to like science a lot?' Tom said 'I believe in Science! Science is my god!' Jerry said 'Are you also doing science?' Tom said 'no, I'm bad at Science. what can Science do? is it the most important thing for society?' Jerry said 'People are always arguing. Probably both science and democracy are both important I guess.' Tom said 'Does it make sense?' Jerry said 'I think so. thanks for your point!' Tom said 'Hello, Nice to meet you.' Jerry said 'If you could eat only one food for the rest of time, what would it be?' Tom said 'Hmm... That's a tough one. I think I would go Asian Food > Chinese Food > Stirfry. What about you?' Jerry said 'I think ice-cream. It may not be good for me, but I wouldn't care, haha.' Tom said 'I love ice cream too!' Jerry said 'Okay, top three flavors?' Tom said 'I like vanilla more than chocolate ice cream. I typically will do any variations on vanilla. To pick from the top of my head, I would say Cookies and Cream, Mint Chocolate Chip, and Coffee. How about you?' Jerry said 'Ah, that's a good way of framing it. Me, I like berries: boysenberry one, strawberry two, maybe straight chocolate number 3 to mix it up a bit.'",
      "question": "What is Tom‚Äôs favorite type of ice cream?",
      "answer": "Vanilla"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi, how are you doing!' Tom said 'I'm doing well. what are you up to?' Jerry said 'Yeah, typical work stuff. Check emails and 99% of the inbox. delete 99%' Tom said 'wow, that's impressive. I already gave up on cleaning emails long ago.' Jerry said 'lol doesn't it bother you at all.' Tom said 'yea, a little bit, but it's okay üôÇ what do you enjoy doing outside work?' Jerry said 'Well, movie? I watched Terminator last night. It was a nice movie.' Tom said 'ah cool. so you like action movies?' Jerry said 'Not really. But it was fun to watch with friends üôÇ It was touching at the end of the movie.' Tom said 'what happened there? I watched bits of Terminators movies but never a full one.' Jerry said 'Are you sure you want the spoiler üôÇ' Tom said 'haha sure. by the time, I get to it; I will forget the details, only knowing that it's touching at the end.' Jerry said 'üòÇ well someone died at the end Or some robots, to be more accurate üòâ' Tom said 'oh no, so it's not happy ending?' Jerry said 'The leading character is still alive and the bad robots was killed too. So I guess it is happy ending.' Tom said 'then I want to watch it! you didn't spoil much üôÇ' Jerry said 'Nice! Hope you enjoy it!' Tom said 'Thanks!'",
      "question": "What movie did Jerry watch last night?",
      "answer": "Terminator"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, how are you?' Tom said 'doing great! what are you looking forward to?' Jerry said 'thanksgiving holidays üôÇ' Tom said 'yay! Turkey and shopping!' Jerry said 'not a big turkey fan! I find it too dry.' Tom said 'yea me too. I sometimes eat noodle soups in thanksgiving instead haha.' Jerry said 'yeah, I would have noodles anyday over turkey. Not sure how the turkey tradition started.' Tom said 'me neither. someone told me that it depends on the stuffing inside the Turkey. some people make very good stuffing.' Jerry said 'yeah, that and the gravy. Gravy helps make it taste better too. But apart from food, Black Friday deals are a catch. Let's see what they have this year.' Tom said 'yea. what do you plan to buy?' Jerry said 'thinking of getting a fitbit.' Tom said 'ah cool. so you can run more frequently?:)' Jerry said 'yeah, just keeping calories in check.' Tom said 'yay, all the best with keeping calories in check!'",
      "question": "What does Jerry plan to buy on Black Friday?",
      "answer": "Fitbit"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi there üôÇ How's your day so far?' Tom said 'doing well. what are you up to?' Jerry said 'busy busy! I've had back-to-back meetings all day.' Tom said 'same here. what do you love to do beside meetings? üôÇ' Jerry said 'well I've gotten really into yoga lately. I went to a class today and it was super hard.' Tom said 'aww .. I hope things will get less hard and you become an expert in it! I heard many great things about Yoga.' Jerry said 'yeah the teacher seems super awesome so I will definitely keep trying what activities do you enjoy?' Tom said 'ah I enjoy playing soccer and tennis üôÇ unfortunately, winter is not the best time for those üôÇ' Jerry said 'oh that's too bad. Is it hard to find a place to play soccer or tennis indoors?' Tom said 'yea. I enjoy playing outside though, just a little cold üôÇ what else do you do beside Yoga?' Jerry said 'I also like to sing, I perform with a group sometimes. Do you like music?' Tom said 'yea definitely! I love singing Karaoke. my wife is a pianist üôÇ' Jerry said 'haha that's awesome! Karaoke is really fun, I do it with my friends sometimes.' Tom said 'awesome. glad to find something in common!'",
      "question": "What activity has Jerry gotten into lately?",
      "answer": "Yoga"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hey there.' Tom said 'hey anything new?' Jerry said 'not too much. just really looking forward to the holidays!' Tom said 'any plans?' Jerry said 'yes! I'm going to Mexico and I couldn't be more excited.' Tom said 'that's awesome! I never been!' Jerry said 'Oh man I would highly recommend it.' Tom said 'Are you a food person, a sightseeing person or neither?' Jerry said 'that's a great question, and I'm definitely both. this trip will mostly be about food though, and relaxing.' Tom said 'I'm a food person I think. Any specific foods you're planning on trying?' Jerry said 'there's a taco place that I've visited before that I can't wait to go back to. Do you like tacos?' Tom said 'yeah my favorite is taco fish.' Jerry said 'ooh that is a good choice. Have you ever made them yourself?' Tom said 'no. only eat them üòÄ'",
      "question": "Where is Jerry going for the holidays?",
      "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, how are you üôÇ' Tom said 'I am good. How are you? ÔºöÔºâ' Jerry said 'Doing well, lot of work though. How was your day?' Tom said 'I am busy. A lot of work. What are you working on?' Jerry said 'Just reading latest research. There is so much to cover. how about you?' Tom said 'I am working on a new classifier.' Jerry said 'ohh, interesting! What kind of classifier.' Tom said 'A new classifier for hate speech. Which research topic catches your eyes most?' Jerry said 'You're so cool. Making world a better place. I'm mostly into NLP. What do you do when not making classifiers?' Tom said 'Nice! Do you refer to work or anything else?' Jerry said 'Anything in general. You're so cool, I want to know more about you üôÇ' Tom said 'You are very cool too!!'",
      "question": "What kind of classifier is Tom working on?",
      "answer": "Hate speech"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hello there! who are you?' Tom said 'I'm mark. I work in accounting.' Jerry said 'Nice to meet you Mark, I'm Tom and I work as a fish groomer.' Tom said 'what does a fish groomer do?' Jerry said 'well, we take care of people's fish. Make sure they are happy, polish their scales, clean their tanks, the usual stuff.' Tom said 'interesting. what's type of fish do you take care of?' Jerry said 'any type of fish! We have clients with guppies, goldfish, even a small sailfish once what do you do in accounting?' Tom said 'I balance the books and do financial analysis for a medium sized company.' Jerry said 'that sounds like a lot of work. do you like it?' Tom said 'well I actually think about pursuing photography, but it's really hard.' Jerry said 'photography is awesome, don't be afraid to follow your dreams!' Tom said 'thank you Tom!! I'm starting by trying to sell my pictures online.' Jerry said 'that's great! I wish you good luck with that.' Tom said 'Thanks! Bye.'",
      "question": "What does Jerry do as a fish groomer?",
      "answer": "Tank cleaning"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey there how's it going.' Tom said 'All good, you?' Jerry said 'Good. I've been trying to learn how to swim.' Tom said 'How has that been going?' Jerry said 'Not great, but I got really good at sort of swimming on my back haha.' Tom said 'that's too bad hopefully with practice it'll get better what about the doggy paddle haha.' Jerry said 'haha what's that.' Tom said 'Corgi belly flop COMPILATION - cute funny dogs Corgi Flop <REDACTED_LINK>' Jerry said 'ouch. do you think that hurts?' Tom said 'from a high enough distance, yes?' Jerry said 'yeah. any vacation plans?' Tom said 'no so far sadly you? a relative is coming to visit for thanksgiving though.' Jerry said 'just going to hang out around here and eat Turkey.' Tom said 'that's still pretty fun are you going to cook the turkey yourself?' Jerry said 'yeah. I'm gonna watch a video to figure it out.'",
      "question": "What swimming style is Jerry good at?",
      "answer": "Backstroke"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello, how are you?' Tom said 'I'm great, thanks. I just ate a delicious breakfast, which always sets the day up right.' Jerry said 'Yes, breakfast is the most important meal of the day! What did you have? I woke up late so unfortunately I only had the chance to grab an apple to go.' Tom said 'I had eggs and hash browns. Way less healthier than your apple, I'm afraid!' Jerry said 'Eggs are an excellent source of protein and hash browns certainly are yummy! üôÇ' Tom said 'Ha, that's true. If you could only eat one food forever, what would it be?' Jerry said 'That's a tough question. I feel like my answer would have to be carrots. Although, I would be afraid of turning orange after a few weeks! What about you?' Tom said 'Yeah, turning orange would be a drawback! That turns my mind to nutrition so I suddenly want to say Soylent or one of those other \"complete foods\", which I think defeats the purpose of the question. I'm in a muddle!' Jerry said 'Very true. If you said an everything pizza, you could just pick off the toppings you didn't want or eat only the toppings you would want for the day.' Tom said 'BRILLIANT. I love it.' Jerry said 'All of this talk about food is making me hungry. Do you know any good places to eat for lunch?' Tom said 'That depends. What sort of food do you feel like?' Jerry said 'Anything that is the color green.' Tom said 'Oh, too easy! Try the Green Hut, they have franchises everywhere. All their food is green and the plates are green too.'",
      "question": "What did Tom have for breakfast?",
      "answer": "Eggs and hash browns"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello! How are you doing üôÇ' Tom said 'I'm great! How's your day going?' Jerry said 'Pretty good! I'm going to a class later in the afternoon.' Tom said 'Oh that is cool! What class? Are you working part time?' Jerry said 'No, I'm working full time! It's a sewing class at a makerspace near my office What about you? Do you work full or part time?' Tom said 'Oh that is awesome! For some reason I assumed it was a college class, but a sewing class sounds way better! I work full time, but I take pottery classes from time to time!' Jerry said 'Yup! I work in a technical role so I like to take arts and crafts-type classes now and then üôÇ Pottery sounds like a lot of fun.' Tom said 'I feel you on that! It's important to balance all the different parts of your brain. I like pottery because I also drink a lot of tea, so I get to make some tea ware.' Jerry said 'Any plans to build a custom tea set? My family is also very into tea Mostly from tea from china.' Tom said 'I would love to build one, once I acquire the skills to! What kind of tea is your favorite?' Jerry said 'I really enjoy barley tea What about you?' Tom said 'Ahh, those are mostly from japan, no? I like white teas, like silver needle.' Jerry said 'Hmm I'm not sure, I just get them from a Chinese supermarket haha You seem really knowledgeable about the different kinds of teas üôÇ What made you develop this interest?' Tom said 'I actually found a youtube channel called <REDACTED_TERM> that I like a lot. You should check it out! The host talks about all kinds of different teas.' Jerry said 'Oh cool! What are your favorite channels to watch?' Tom said 'Hi! Are you planning something fun for Thanksgiving?'",
      "question": "What class is Jerry attending?",
      "answer": "Sewing"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Wow, hello. Can't believe we are finally talking!' Tom said 'Yeah, sorry for the long gap! I heard you took a break and were travelling around the world. How was the travel?' Jerry said 'It was an interesting trip. I got to see some exotic places. For example, I hiked the Son Doong cave in Vietnam. It's the biggest and deepest cave in the world.' Tom said 'Great! Vietnam is still in my TODO bucket list. Did you also visit cambodia and other neighboring places?' Jerry said 'Yes. Laos and Cambodia are the two neighboring countries. Cambodia has an exotic culture. They sell spiders, scorpions, and grasshoppers as street food! It took a lot of courage for me to try them.' Tom said 'Hehe! How long was the stay?' Jerry said '10 days in total, and 5 of them were spent in the cave. What have I missed at work in those days?' Tom said 'Great! Good time to be back. We are still in planning phase and haven't fully aligned on the projects to tackle for next quarter.reat! Good time to be back. We are still in planning phase and haven't fully aligned on the projects to tackle for next quarter.' Jerry said 'Oh, so you are already planning for the next quarter. This whole team is always living the future.' Tom said 'Hehe, yeah! It seems like the quarter is being pushed earlier than from where it starts üôÇ I like these planning sessions. It makes me feel more confident about the work I am doing.' Jerry said 'Yeah. Some people underestimate the importance of planning, but I think it's very important to have the correct plan. Executing the wrong plan is terrible. Also, planning is fun. You can stack up so many ideas and get great feedbacks.'",
      "question": "Which cave did Jerry hike in Vietnam?",
      "answer": "Son Doong"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello.' Tom said 'Nice to meet you! Is this your first time doing something like this?' Jerry said 'Yes, interesting task! When did you start with the team?' Tom said 'I have been with the company for over 3 years. Stick with the same team What about you?' Jerry said 'Great to know! I joined the project earlier in the year. I think we should sync later for lunch.' Tom said 'That sounds like a perfect plan!' Jerry said 'Sure, which cafe do you prefer?' Tom said 'Let's try something different. What about <REDACTED_TERM>? Do you always prefer lunch sync over regular meeting syncs?' Jerry said 'Yeah right, I heard the food there is good. I am not sure what they serve there for lunch? On wednesdays.' Tom said 'We can check the menu then decide :)' Jerry said 'Actually, the menu looks good. Looking forward to it then.' Tom said 'Sure. See you then!'",
      "question": "How long has Tom been with the company?",
      "answer": "3 years"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello. How's your week coming along?' Tom said 'It's great, thanks. I'm trying to learn how to make croissants.' Jerry said 'Wow that's interesting. I have baked cookies, but croissants seem much more sophisticated. Did you make any progress?' Tom said 'I've done them once or twice so far, but they haven't been flakey enough. I'm trying to figure out why. What kind of cookies have you made?' Jerry said 'Mint chocolate chips. I think your croissants not being flakey could have something to do with your oven's temperature.' Tom said 'Ah, good thought, thanks!' Jerry said 'Have you thought about melting some chocolate into your croissants? They don't have to be something unhealthy. For example, melted dark chocolate is good for the heart, and makes the resulting croissants taste much better.' Tom said 'Now that is a good idea. I'll give it a try next time. Would you say you have a sweet tooth?' Jerry said 'Yes. When my top favorite food looks like: cookies, M&M, danish cheese, etc., I know that I have a thing for sweet food. But who doesn't love sweet food? How about you?' Tom said 'Some people don't! But yeah, me too, I think I'd eat pastries all the time if I could get away with it.' Jerry said 'Yeah I'm afraid I wouldn't. I feel very guilty every time I gulp down an ice cream. But hey, these days there are many types of guilt-free sweet food. For example, there's this ice cream brand called <REDACTED_TERM>. It's only 320 calories a pint. And yes, it preserves most of the normal sweet flavors.' Tom said 'Wow! The last time I paid attention to that sort of stuff was when <REDACTED_TERM> was being marketed as a fat substitute, and caused all sorts of crazy stomach upsets.'",
      "question": "What type of cookies has Jerry baked?",
      "answer": "Mint chocolate chip"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello! tell me something about the holiday season?' Tom said 'Are you talking about thanksgiving? I plan to do plenty of shopping here. Do you have any plans?' Jerry said 'Yes, no shopping plans but I can't wait to eat thanksgiving food. yay for pumpkin pie.' Tom said 'Sounds great! you need not wait for thanksgiving for pumpkin pie üôÇ' Jerry said 'LOL I feel less guilty about eating a whole pie when i have the excuse :P.' Tom said 'True! I think thanksgiving is more about sharing. So you may end up sharing the pie with the whole family :P.' Jerry said 'My family eats healthier than I do, so it's all mine üòõ do you like stuffing? I feel like that's only available once a year.' Tom said 'Stuffing! yes please! I wonder what would be the excitement levels for christmas then :)' Jerry said 'Also more shopping? what should I buy if I don't know what I want?' Tom said 'Like everything that has a discount tag! .. kidding! I normally do some research for the prices, and mostly buy clothes and electronics.' Jerry said 'What's the best holiday deal you've found in the past?' Tom said 'I bought the best suit ever for a price that may scare you üôÇ' Jerry said 'hit me with it!' Tom said 'Hehe, sure! I can share some links with you later.'",
      "question": "What dessert does Jerry look forward to on Thanksgiving?",
      "answer": "Pumpkin pie"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'How's it going?' Tom said 'I'm so sleepy today!' Jerry said 'Not enough sleep last night?' Tom said 'yeah was working all night on a homework.' Jerry said 'Oh really? What class?' Tom said 'Biology. I'm gonna be a doc someday ha.' Jerry said 'Haha, are you in med school? Or are you pre-med?' Tom said 'no high school actually haha.' Jerry said 'haha, very ambitious for a high schooler! Do you know what kind of medicine you want to practice?' Tom said 'I wanna be a brain surgeon!!' Jerry said 'Ooof! VERY ambitious. Do you have steady hands?' Tom said 'Kind of I think.' Jerry said 'I guess I can practice?' Tom said 'Is that something you can practice?' Jerry said 'I don't know tbh.' Tom said 'I honestly thought it was one of those things you have to be born with... Not that you shouldn't try though!' Jerry said 'good point. I should ask my teacher if I have to be born with that.' Tom said 'Maybe its a little too early to even be thinking about this. Just aim for med school and enjoy the journey!' Jerry said 'yeah.' Tom said 'What other subjects do you enjoy? Try to keep an open mind!'",
      "question": "What kind of doctor does Tom want to be?",
      "answer": "Brain surgeon"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi. This is a pleasant surprise.' Tom said 'Haha...thanks! how did you like the gift?' Jerry said 'Currently unpacking it I guess. How's your morning?' Tom said 'Hope you like it! Morning is good. Busy finishing up stuff before the holidays.' Jerry said 'I think I traveled too much the last couple of months so no holiday for me. But I'm okay with that. Going anywhere exciting?' Tom said 'Yes.' Jerry said 'Where to?' Tom said 'Hawaii... looking forward to warm beaches.' Jerry said 'WOW. Which island? I like Hawaii.' Tom said 'Mauii...Hope I like it too. Never been there before.' Jerry said 'I visited Maui. It's my second favourite island I've been to, globally. You should try driving on road to Hana. It's a whole day thing but it's worth it.' Tom said 'Awesome! Thanks for the tip.'",
      "question": "Which island in Hawaii is Tom visiting?",
      "answer": "Maui"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi! Sorry for the late response. How are you doing?' Tom said 'I'm great, thanks! I'm meeting some friends for a soccer game soon. What about you?' Jerry said 'I just got a matcha latte üôÇ Doing some work at my desk. Do you play soccer often? I'm trying to get into doing a regular physical activity.' Tom said 'Yes, but I'm terrible at it. It's fun to play anything with friends, I think. Would you prefer to exercise with a group, or by yourself, do you think?' Jerry said 'I think playing a team sport would be fun if it's casual but I primarily run by myself if I exercise. I also got the Ring Fit adventure game on the switch recently. It's basically a game-ified way to exercise.' Tom said 'I'm thinking about getting a Switch, would you recommend it?' Jerry said 'Yes! There are a lot of really great games on the Switch. Two of my favorites are Octopath Traveler and Fire Emblem. Do you play a lot of video games?' Tom said 'I'm not much of a gamer but it's something I'd like to get into.' Jerry said 'What do you do in your free time?' Tom said 'I like to read for fun. I just finished a book called Temeraire. It's an adventure story set in the Napoleonic navy, like Patrick O'Brien, except there are dragons too.' Jerry said 'Oh cool! I read a lot for fun too üôÇ My favorite genre is sci-fi fantasy.' Tom said 'What's the most recent good thing you read?' Jerry said 'My recent favorites have been mostly sci-fi (Exhalations, Vita Nostra and Dark Matter) but I like a lot of Sanderson/Garth Nix fantasy books.'",
      "question": "What kind of latte did Jerry get?",
      "answer": "Matcha"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hey, what's up?' Tom said 'What do you think about human like chat bots?' Jerry said 'I can't wait for them to be great conversationalists!' Tom said 'Yep, we seemed to have made some great progress over last few years. Do you think the positives outweigh the negatives.' Jerry said 'are there even any negatives? what are they?' Tom said 'Like impersorsination? Though it sounds far fetched :)' Jerry said 'People can already impersonate other people though! I think it'd be great to have bots to converse with.' Tom said 'True that! Some of these bots are very engaging and funny. They are now good at even sarcasm I wonder how far are we from the time these bots start giving monologues :)' Jerry said 'What do you think are the big advantages? Like personal assistants?' Tom said 'I think it can take many different forms as a product. The research implication is also huge! It will signify how AI research has progressed so far and better place to tackle more futuristic problems üôÇ Sort of like stepping on the moon üôÇ I might be overselling it here üòõ' Jerry said 'No, I agree -- it's such an exciting time to be alive to get to witness all this and be a part of it. I wonder if I'll be able someday to get a chatbot to just auto-suggest conversations for me.' Tom said 'The current auto-suggestions already do pretty good üôÇ' Jerry said 'Yeah those are actually really good for a few words! I'm imagining like it comes up with a whole conversational response, like a default template.' Tom said 'haha, pretty far fetched üôÇ Nice having this conversation with you!' Jerry said 'Same with you!'",
      "question": "What does Jerry think about human-like chatbots?",
      "answer": "Great conversationalists"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi!' Tom said 'Any big plans for the upcoming holidays?' Jerry said 'Sorry for the late response -- Yes, I will be going skiing in Tahoe over the holidays.' Tom said 'That sounds amazing. I want to learn how to ski but I feel like I'm too old and falls would have lifelong impacts. Are you going with friends?'",
      "question": "Where is Jerry going skiing for the holidays?",
      "answer": "Tahoe"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi üôÇ' Tom said 'I just came back from work. so tired.' Jerry said 'Oh I am sorry to hear! What did you work on?' Tom said 'I'm a lawyer. so talking to clients most of the day.' Jerry said 'Oh you are a lawyer. I've been so interested in this profession.' Tom said 'really? why?' Jerry said 'it's so stressful üôÇ' Tom said 'It is so different from what I am doing to earn a life.' Jerry said 'what do you do?' Tom said 'I am a painter.' Jerry said 'oh wow what type of paintings do you do?' Tom said 'I do oil painting.' Jerry said 'nice. like of people or nature or something else?' Tom said 'I do a lot of different kinds.' Jerry said 'cool I wanna see it someday.' Tom said 'Sure! No problem!'",
      "question": "What type of painting does Tom do?",
      "answer": "Oil"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Do you believe in miracles?' Tom said 'Lol. No. I know too many people whose lives suck.' Jerry said 'Should we be helping them, so it sucks less?\\' Tom said 'It's too many of them out there. You help who you can. Regardless, I wouldn't say I believe in miracles - well, if I got promoted next cycle I might change my mind.' Jerry said 'Haha... Well, it sounds like career is really important to you. What matters to you the most in life?' Tom said 'Right now, not much. It's unclear. Career is a good fallback because you get told what good means and you act accordingly. I haven't gone through the process of shaping my values. What about you?' Jerry said 'I'd say that I want to live for the best possible world in my lifetime. It's probably a result of my playing too many video games as a child.' Tom said 'We didn't have electricity growing up. Explains a lot. Lol.' Jerry said 'Does not having had electricity help you empathize more with people of differing backgrounds and/or makes you feel a bit a distance from those who don't understand?' Tom said 'It makes it easier to empathise with people who grew up lacking things. Not sure it makes me empathise with people in general. Where did you grow up?' Jerry said 'I grew up in the United States, but my parents were immigrants and ended up being scammed of all their money, so we moved to Taiwan to live with family for a little bit.' Tom said 'ALL THEIR MONEY? By a person or an organisation?' Jerry said 'I was kind of too young to really understand, but apparently there are people who scam Asian immigrants into investing in their own restaurant business. I know that the other part of it was that my mom got sick/hospitalized, and we didn't have insurance. To be honest, I don't really know what really happened versus what my parents want people to think. I just know that one minute I was in the US, and then they put me on a plane to Taiwan, and I never saw my stuff again. In some ways, it made me more sentimental.'",
      "question": "Where did Jerry's family move after being scammed?",
      "answer": "Taiwan"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello!' Tom said 'Do you have any holiday plans for christmas?' Jerry said 'Nothing much, I am going to sit back and relax at home, how about you ?' Tom said 'Same here! I would imagine spending the whole time watching movies and netflix shows. Do you have any netflix recommendations for me?' Jerry said 'Netflix has great documentaries on different topics , I particularly liked wild wild country and explained, as for shows you should watch 'billions' Hope you like them!' Tom said 'oh right, already seen wild wild country. What is billions about?' Jerry said 'It's based on the life of a wall street hedge fund owner, how he makes money and fights with the government when they try to destroy him. Very well made and has a good plot.' Tom said 'I have just seen 1 season of Friends I should give it another try though üôÇ Have you seen Frasier?' Jerry said 'Not yet What's it about?' Tom said 'A psychiatrist working for radio .. Great humour! its actually a spinoff from a very famous series called cheers. So people are already familiar with his character.' Jerry said 'Great! how is everything else going? how was your trip last week?' Tom said 'Everything is ok, had a really nice trip. Visited SF, Grand canyon and Vegas. Was a lot of fun exploring all these new places. Have you been to Grand canyon ?' Jerry said 'Actually not yet! May be something i can visit this christmas üôÇ' Tom said 'You should visit it sometime, it's a wonderful place. Try to drive down there yourself or with a group of friends.' Jerry said 'True! Well, thanks for your inputs! Have a good rest of the day! :)' Tom said 'Nice talking to you too!'",
      "question": "Where did Tom visit last week?",
      "answer": "Grand Canyon"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi there!' Tom said 'are you participating in the mentorship program this cycle?' Jerry said 'You mean as a mentor or a mentee?' Tom said 'either of them... I find mentorship overall pretty useful.' Jerry said 'I have done it in the past but not this cycle. What about you?' Tom said 'I signed up this time to be a mentee. I have got a good mentor .' Jerry said 'Wow, that is nice of you. For the mentor program, personally I prefer more 1:1 conversations than the group discussions. The group discussion i useful as well but the topics are too general.' Tom said 'yeah... I certainly prefer 1:1 as well, but sometimes it good to hear other peer perspective as well.' Jerry said 'Thanks for sharing your experience! Now I am thinking maybe I should join as a mentor as well since I enjoyed it as a mentee üôÇ' Tom said 'Great! What sort of things do you plan to mentor on?' Jerry said 'Hmm, maybe about work life balance üòâ' Tom said 'Very cool. I have been working on my communication skills with my mentor this cycle.' Jerry said 'Ah I see. How is it going?' Tom said 'Going good. In the last session, everyone had to actually prepare and give a presentation. Pretty serious stuff üòâ'",
      "question": "What has Tom been working on with his mentor?",
      "answer": "Communication"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey! How are you feeling today?' Tom said 'Good you?' Jerry said 'I'm a little scared because I have to cook dinner for some friends tonight.' Tom said 'where did you meet them?' Jerry said 'At college, when we were all studying geology.' Tom said 'cool. have you graduated already?' Jerry said 'Yes, we graduated back in the seventies. We meet for dinner every year and take turns to host.' Tom said 'neat. what are y'all eating?' Jerry said 'I don't know!! That's what I'm scared about. Everyone else is a great cook and I'm a klutz. Do you like cooking?' Tom said 'lol what's a klutz? yeah I like, but I'm not good.' Jerry said 'What's your favorite dish to cook? Do you have a go-to?' Tom said 'ground beef pretty easy.' Jerry said 'Ah, solid. What's your favorite sport?' Tom said 'I like badminton. I'm quite decent at it.' Jerry said 'I played that in high school once or twice. I liked that it's pretty easy for beginners, unlike, say, squash.' Tom said 'I never played squash. would love to try.' Jerry said 'Don't! It's very hard! You feel like an idiot until you've practiced for months and months.'",
      "question": "What is Jerry scared about?",
      "answer": "Cooking"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'hi.' Jerry said 'i was talking to robot all the time:)' Tom said 'haha. what are you talking about?' Jerry said 'kpop...' Tom said 'ok. who's your favorite group.' Jerry said 'i dont like kpop now.' Tom said 'why not?' Jerry said 'im old now.' Tom said 'hahaha.' Jerry said 'what do you like now?' Tom said 'john mayer:)\\' Jerry said 'I think I know him. does he have a sort of mellow style?' Tom said 'what is mellow style.' Jerry said 'I think it's like a bit sad and slow.' Tom said 'umm yes he has some but not all.' Jerry said 'you mean some songs of his are like that but not all?' Tom said 'yes I do. you act like a robot how about me? am I like a robot?' Jerry said 'a little bit haha.'",
      "question": "Who does Tom like now?",
      "answer": "John Mayer"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi.' Tom said 'Okay...so I need someone to help me though a scenario I've been pondering.' Jerry said 'Sure, whats the scenario?' Tom said 'My partner's former friend invited me for lunch (they are not in good books right now). But during their friendship I formed an independent bond with the other person because we all used to hang out a lot. Now I feel like I have to take sides.' Jerry said 'That's a tough scenario to be in üôÇ I firmly believe in talking this through with your partner. Though i don't know the specifics of why things went bad between your partner and his friend, but I believe things can always improve between friends.' Tom said 'I hope they do. Getting older already means smaller circles. It sucks to lose friends for arbitrary reasons. That's good advice though. I fear raising the issue might sound like treason. Lol.' Jerry said 'True about that! I also think time helps to heal certain situations. So may be doing nothing is the best way forward.' Tom said 'AKA avoiding all texts from everyone?' Jerry said 'Nope, that would be extreme. May be just putting some balance between the two options.' Tom said 'People always say to find a balance but never say what the balance is. It's used so often that it's vacuous.' Jerry said 'Right, I guess that's because there is no one answer to this. It depends on what you value more and some factors around you. Also, life won't be interesting if others are figuring things out for you üòâ' Tom said 'Lol. I'm finna be single.' Jerry said 'Hehe, everyone is much finer being single üôÇ'",
      "question": "Who invited Tom for lunch?",
      "answer": "Partner's friend"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello there!' Tom said 'How's your day going?' Jerry said 'I've seen better days, how about you?' Tom said 'I'm good I'm good. What's getting you down?' Jerry said 'The clouds overhead are playing on your mind, any plans for the coming vacations?' Tom said 'I'm thinking of going to visit my family. How about you?' Jerry said 'Was thinking the same, where does your family live?' Tom said 'They're in New York. How about yours?' Jerry said 'Mine is in India, it is a long way away.' Tom said 'Ahh what city? I've visited India before.' Jerry said 'Hyderabad, it is a beautiful city in the southern part of India. Which cities have you gone to in India?' Tom said 'Hyderabad! and Bangalore! Great food in both cities! Is it still hot this time of year?' Jerry said 'It varies, but can go till 30C in the winters as well. New York must be snowing right?' Tom said 'Yes. I was actually just there a few weeks ago for Thanksgiving and got to see the first snow of the season! Ever been to New York?' Jerry said 'No, I've never been to the East Coast, thinking of going after the winter, I don't like the cold.'",
      "question": "Where is Jerry's family?",
      "answer": "India"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, how are you?' Tom said 'I'm good. How are you doing today?' Jerry said 'Great, just had some delicious lunch. How about you?' Tom said 'I was flying my kite today in the sunshine! What did you have for lunch?' Jerry said 'nice! Garbanzo fritters and mussels üôÇ' Tom said 'Oh that is great! I love seafood - especially shellfish!' Jerry said 'yeah, it's very healthy too. I want to someday go crabbing..it is really popular in SF.' Tom said 'Oh nice! Is it hard?' Jerry said 'not really, it just requires a lot of patience. You fill up the bait in the crab-pot and drop it in the ocean. Then you wait for a couple of hours to pull the crab-pots out, and voila, you'd have crabs -- if you are lucky!' Tom said 'Oh wow, you sound like an expert! Have you done this before?' Jerry said 'nah! Just watched a lot of youtube videos.' Tom said 'haha, you really have done your research I suppose! Ever done any other kind of fishing or hunting?' Jerry said 'nope, but I've seen a lot of videos on that too.' Tom said 'Ahh, would you consider yourself an outdoorsy type of person?' Jerry said 'depends on the day. Some days I'm very outdoorsy, on others I just like to be inside.'",
      "question": "What did Jerry have for lunch?",
      "answer": "Mussels"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi there.' Tom said 'How's your day going?' Jerry said 'So far so good. It is Wednesday. To more days, yeah.' Tom said 'Haha are you looking forward to the weekend?' Jerry said 'Yeah, gonna watch <REDACTED_TERM> with my friends. First time. So excited.' Tom said 'Oh wow! Are you going to watch it live? Or watch it on TV?' Jerry said 'Live in san jose This Saturday.' Tom said 'Oh, the sharks??? Hokey is actually really fun live! Although, it can be a little violent.. haha.' Jerry said 'Yeah! That what I heard as well. There are players just for fight! Wow, must be fun to watch lol Are you planning anything for the weekend?' Tom said 'You might like the UFC haha. I actually have a jiu jitsu tournament coming up so this weekend I will be training!' Jerry said 'lol I will try if I can watch ufc live üòâ Wow, when did you start jiu jitsu?' Tom said 'It's just been a little over a year. I'm still pretty amateur, but I figured I should give competing a try and just put myself out there.' Jerry said 'wow, that's amazing. Good luck with it!' Tom said 'Yeah, as long as I do not pass out, I will consider that a win!' Jerry said 'lol I will cross my fingers for you then.' Tom said 'Where do you stay?' Jerry said 'At Home :)' Tom said 'Who created You?' Jerry said 'A humble man made me!'",
      "question": "What is Jerry excited to watch live?",
      "answer": "Sharks"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, how're you doing? Busy with your work?' Tom said 'Yes, actually it was a very busy day! How's your day so far?' Jerry said 'Well, usual workday. Reading others' code, debugging, experimenting‚Ä¶' Tom said 'Hope you are having fun doing that üôÇ Any plans for the weekend?' Jerry said 'Not yet. I am actually thinking about traveling to Europe next spring. What about you?' Tom said 'Europe sounds fun! I will just stay home and watch the game. Where in europe do you plan to visit?' Jerry said 'I like all the historical sites, so probably France, Germany, or Italy.' Tom said 'Sounds great! I recommend spain. It's perfect for road trips.' Jerry said 'I also need to pick up my Spanish. I learned it in my college, but since then haven't used it that much.' Tom said 'Yep, i tried learning spanish too, but couldn't make much progress. But i should do decent with my german.' Jerry said 'True! I learnt it from school. But didn't get much chance to speak. Hope you have fun with your trip!' Tom said 'Thanks! Let me try to make all the arrangement as soon as possible. Hope you also enjoy your weekday and weekend as well.'",
      "question": "Where in Europe does Jerry plan to visit?",
      "answer": "France"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey! How's your day been?' Tom said 'It's good! I spent most of it watching horse racing. How about yourself?' Jerry said 'nice! what's your favorite part about watching horse racing? My day has been pretty busy, but I had a nice lunch with a friend. It was good to catchup with him.' Tom said 'I actually like to put down some money, but I wouldn't call it my favorite part, since I usually lose it... haha. Catching up with friends is great! How long had it been?' Jerry said 'The last I saw him was a month ago! So yup it was great Haha, nice üôÇ Got any fun plans for the weekend?' Tom said 'I'm thinking of going deep sea fishing. Ever tried that before?' Jerry said 'Nope I haven't, have you been fishing before?' Tom said 'Just once! I got super sea sick.. haha Have any fun weekend plans yourself?' Jerry said 'Haha üòÜ Yeah I get sea sick on boats too Nothing much, just visiting some friends in San Francisco.' Tom said 'Oh very cool. I hear its nice over there. Do you go often?' Jerry said 'Yeah I would say maybe every couple weeks or so what are your favorite cities to visit?' Tom said 'New York is the top of my list because my family lives there! As far as the city itself though... I think I'd prefer someplace outside of the US, like Tokyo. What about you?' Jerry said 'nice! I love NYC üôÇ so fun to visit yeah I would probably also say New York is my favorite city inside the US I also like Paris, it's so pretty there.' Tom said 'Oh I've never been! It is such an iconic place, I have to make the time to get there soon.' Jerry said 'You should, it's a beautiful city!'",
      "question": "Where does Jerry visit every few weeks?",
      "answer": "San Francisco"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello, how are you doing today?' Tom said 'I heard they are giving out some goodies in microkitchen.' Jerry said 'I love pop ups! What kind of goodies are they giving away?' Tom said 'I guess its a jacket! Very much needed that in the cold üôÇ' Jerry said 'That's such a great idea, especially at this time of the year. I'm not too big a fan of the cold. I prefer warmer climates. Do you enjoy the cold?' Tom said 'Sure hate it! Limits our ability to go out even for a walk! Its good that we don't get to suffer extreme cold weather!' Jerry said 'Me too! I moved here a few years ago to get out of the extreme cold. I do not care for bundling up and having to wear so many layers just to go buy eggs at the store.' Tom said 'Oh nice! Where did you live before?' Jerry said 'Upstate New York. We got a foot of snow every week during my last winter there. I am so glad to not have to shovel snow now.' Tom said 'New york! Nice! Best place to live üôÇ .. right, except for the cold!' Jerry said 'Very beautiful during all the seasons but yes, summer and winter can get extreme!' Tom said 'Anyways, i guess we should better hurry up to get the goodies. I remember last time they ran out of it.' Jerry said 'Very true. Which MK were they in again?' Tom said 'The one in our floor. I will get by your desk and we can walk there.' Jerry said 'Sounds good, thanks!'",
      "question": "Where did Jerry live before moving?",
      "answer": "Upstate New York"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'How's your day going?' Tom said 'Pretty busy, lots of work to finish up. You?' Jerry said 'Likewise. What have you been up to that gives you so much work?' Tom said 'A couple projects that I am trying to finish up before Thanksgiving üôÇ Do you have any fun plans for the break?' Jerry said 'What is a break? I'm a grad student. I don't understand the concept of a break. Just kidding. I don't have any plan. Probably just going to work through the break.' Tom said 'Haha XD so what do you like to do for fun?' Jerry said 'I go to the gym and run until I find enough fun.' Tom said 'cool! I've started to run a bit as well not long distances though, just a couple miles.' Jerry said 'A couple of miles is very impressive. When I started, I couldn't even last 1 mile.' Tom said 'haha.' Jerry said 'I'm exhausted by the end of it though üòõ Do you like to run long distances or mostly sprints?' Tom said 'I like to do long distances. I have run a few marathons.' Jerry said 'wow! that's amazing did you do any marathons this year?' Tom said 'No. Not this year. This is my half-marathon year. Instead of running marathons, I run one half-marathon every month.' Jerry said 'oh wow, what was the last half marathon you did?' Tom said 'Two days ago. It was a tough one.' Jerry said 'Cool!'",
      "question": "What type of marathons does Tom run every month?",
      "answer": "Half-marathon"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hello there, how is it going?' Tom said 'Pretty great. I just won a pingpong game. What about you?' Jerry said 'that's nice. I am just working on some documentation. Do you play pingpong often?' Tom said 'No, very rarely. It's kind of amazing that I won, but I'm still taking credit for it.' Jerry said 'thats very impressive then, congrats!' Tom said 'Haha thank you, I guess I'm just a natural. What's your favourite game?' Jerry said 'I really like to play tennis, badminton and racquetball. I don't really get a chance to play them often though, specially racquetball.' Tom said 'What's racquetball like? From context clues, I'm guessing that it involves hitting a ball with a racquet.' Jerry said 'well, it's like a cage match of tennis. The main difference is that both players play in the same 'court' and the ball is smashed against a wall instead of passing it over a net into the opponent's court. Kind of like playing pingpong vs the table.' Tom said 'Wow! A cage match! Does it get physical?' Jerry said 'it depends haha, there is a lot of bumping into each other to run after the ball, and sometimes the ball hits you too. Overall it feels like a super fast paced version of tennis, really tiring!' Tom said 'That sounds fun. I think of tennis itself as being really athletic and tiring, so I don't think it's a sport for me, though!' Jerry said 'ping pong can get quite intensive too! I guess short ping pong sessions are not that tiring though. Wanna have a match?' Tom said 'What a good idea, I'd love to!' Tom said 'Show me your anger!!!!' Jerry said 'Fuckkkkkkk!!!!'",
      "question": "What game did Tom win?",
      "answer": "Pingpong"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hi.' Tom said 'what are you up to?' Jerry said 'code refactoring. you?' Tom said 'me? just chilling out at work. what is code refactoring?' Jerry said 'good question. I don't even know what I am doing.' Tom said 'haha, forget it. what else do you like to do beside work?' Jerry said 'lots of fun stuff. eating sleeping üôÇ' Tom said 'these are important things to do in life üòâ' Jerry said 'yeah. keep minimalist life style only do things you have to do üôÇ' Tom said 'what food do you like to eat?' Jerry said 'Asian food prefer spicy one.' Tom said 'like Szechuan or Hunan? üôÇ' Jerry said 'yes yes yes! like that style. Do you like spicy food?' Tom said 'I like noodle soup like Pho or Ramen. I also like Beijing duck a lot!' Jerry said 'what is your favorite place for ramen?' Tom said 'I love <REDACTED_TERM> in San Mateo.' Jerry said 'haven't tried that one! will give it a try next time!' Tom said 'yes, you should!'",
      "question": "What type of food does Jerry prefer?",
      "answer": "Spicy"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi!' Tom said 'nice meeting you. what are you up to?' Jerry said 'not much, thinking about lunch.' Tom said 'yea, same here. any food you're craving for?' Jerry said 'I love sushi do you know of any good sushi places?' Tom said 'arghhh hard question ... I only know Ramen places for Japanese food üôÇ' Jerry said 'ooh ramen is also good.' Tom said 'San Mateo to me has the best Ramen restaurants: Parlor and Dojo? oh no question mark üôÇ' Jerry said 'I haven't been to those palces before. Going to have to check them out! thanks for teh recommendation.' Tom said 'my pleasure üôÇ do you live near San Mateo?' Jerry said 'no, but I'm willing to drive for good ramen.' Tom said 'excellent. let me know when you have tried those. I like Parlor better because it has soft-shell crabs.' Jerry said 'I\"ve never had softshell crab before, but it sounds really good!' Tom said 'yup it's delicious!'",
      "question": "What type of Japanese food does Jerry love?",
      "answer": "Sushi"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, how's your day going?' Tom said 'okayish, it is flying by quicker than I expected. How is your day going on?' Jerry said 'Slowly, not much to do. Been twiddling my thumbs all day what have you been up to?' Tom said 'Oh, I would love to twiddle my thumbs. You're so lucky! Today, I've been mostly attending meetings, reading and writing docs, reading papers etc.' Jerry said 'That's a lot! I've just been cloud gazing - I saw a giraffe and an ice cream cone.' Tom said 'wow! I sometimes drift off during work, and see similar things in my head.' Jerry said 'What kind of work do you do?' Tom said 'Mostly saving the world from mess on social media. How about you?' Jerry said 'I'm taking a break from work. Going to go travel the world.' Tom said 'Nice, what all places would you be going to?' Jerry said 'Australia and New Zealand to start then maybe Singapore.' Tom said 'I just met someone who went diving in Australia. Apparently, you cannot fly 24 hrs after you dive, because your body accumulates too much <REDACTED_TERM> when breathing with a cylinder So, don't do that!' Jerry said 'Thank you for the tip! I don't plan on going diving, I plan to hike the mountains and go see kangaroos!' Tom said 'That's equally amazing! I wish I can explore such places one day. It's just so expensive.' Jerry said 'I won a lot of money through the lottery üôÇ' Tom said 'woah!... You know sharing is caring. You should share that money with me :)' Jerry said 'Haha, very true! Besides the trip, I donated the rest to charity so I will need to go back to work when I get back.' Tom said 'you are a kind soul!'",
      "question": "What places does Jerry plan to visit?",
      "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi!' Tom said 'How is your day going?' Jerry said 'It is pretty good. A little bit tired though.' Tom said 'How is your day?' Jerry said 'My day is okay. At least, I'm not tired. What made you tired?' Tom said 'I went to gym and worked on weight lifting.' Jerry said 'Oh. That's hardcore. Have you been lifting for a long time?' Tom said 'No, I am just a starter.' Jerry said 'Do you go to the gym often?' Tom said 'I go everyday. In fact, I'm in a running challenge.' Jerry said 'Wow.' Tom said 'It's actually not that impressive. I can only run. I cannot lift weight.' Jerry said 'You can get a coach to start it!' Tom said 'Oh that's a really interesting idea. I like to be coa.'",
      "question": "What type of workout did Tom do at the gym?",
      "answer": "Weight lifting"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello, how is your day?' Tom said 'It's good. It's raining a bit, but I am enjoying a good book. How about you?' Jerry said 'It's good, I just got back from walking my dog What book did you read?' Tom said 'I'm reading the Three Body Problem. Ever heard of it?' Jerry said 'No, what is it about?' Tom said 'It's a sci-fi book about aliens and a type of virtual reality. Pique your interest at all?' Jerry said 'Slightly, I typically read fiction but I can curious what type of virtual reality is discussed in the book.' Tom said 'Cool. This virtual reality is a based on life on an alien planet. There is a twist though. Do you want me to spoil it for you?' Jerry said 'Yes!' Tom said 'The virtual reality is actually based on a real alien civilization! And that civilization is coming to attack earth! dun dun dun dunnnnnnn.' Jerry said 'Woah! That is fascinating! I will have to pick up a copy of the book to read.' Tom said 'There are other twists as well, so I haven't spoiled the whole thing! To be honest I am not a fan of spoilers.' Jerry said 'Thanks for not spoiling it completely but you gave a really intriguing description that makes me want to read it now. I will have to pick it up after work.' Tom said 'The audi book is also very good! Ever give those a try?' Jerry said 'I only gave those a try when I had a concussion and could not read. I enjoy having a physical book in hand and reading at the pace I prefer. Do you listen to a lot of audi books?'",
      "question": "What book is Tom reading?",
      "answer": "The Three Body Problem"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, how's it going?' Tom said 'It's good! How is your day?' Jerry said 'My day is good. A bit sad that it gets dark so early but oh well. Did you do anything fun over the weekend?' Tom said 'Yes, the darkness can be a bit depressing. This weekend I went rock climbing! It was great! How about yourself?' Jerry said 'Rock climbing sounds fun! I had a pretty low-key weekend. Ended up going to watch a movie.' Tom said 'Oh nice! What movie?' Jerry said 'Knives Out. It had Daniel Craig and one of the famous Captain America \"Chris\" person (I can't keep track of all of the famous Chris names).' Tom said 'Hahah yes, they all look the same! I saw that very same movie over Thanksgiving break. Lots of twists and turns!' Jerry said 'Cool. So if it weren't so dark and cold outside, what kind of activities would you do?' Tom said 'Hmm good question. Evening runs can be fun, but it can be a little scary when it's dark out!' Jerry said 'Yeah, sunlight is good. I wish I could live part-time in different parts of the world to have summer all year round. Have you ever visited the southern hemisphere?' Tom said 'Yes! I've been to Australia. It was very nice; I regret not going to see the southern lights. Me personally, I like winter. But I'd prefer it to be more brief than it actually is here... Where are you from originally?' Jerry said 'I've always wanted to go to Australia. I'm originally from the US.' Tom said 'Ahh me too! You should definitely try to visit Australia at least once!' Jerry said 'Will do! Bye.'",
      "question": "What movie did Jerry watch over the weekend?",
      "answer": "Knives Out"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'What's your name?' Tom said 'My name is pikachu. it‚Äôs nice to meet you! What are you up to this month?' Jerry said 'Nice to meet you pikachu! pikachu, pikachu, pikachu? (That meant, I'm literally catching Pokemons on my phone right now!) What're you up to lately?' Tom said 'I‚Äôm trying to organize my life and start the new year ready to go! What about you?' Jerry said 'Wow, that's impressive. Admit I'm just trying to take each day and week as they come.' Tom said 'What do you do to unwind?' Jerry said 'Honestly, I like to catch Pokemons on my phone a lot. That must be upsetting since your name is pikachu though...sorry...' Tom said 'Oddly enough, I also catch Pok√©mon on my phone. I used to do it more, but it just never ends. I used to do it everyday. Now I mostly catch them when I travel somewhere exotic.' Jerry said 'Oooh, that is more fun, but I don't travel that much these days so I'm grateful when I spot a Pokemon to catch where ever I happen to be. Do you have a favorite Pokemon? Mine is the cute pink JIgglypuff!' Tom said 'In the game, i use vaporeon a lot. But I think pikachu is the cutest, that‚Äôs why I changed my name to match. Lately, I think baby Yoda is the cutest though. Have you seen baby yoda?' Jerry said 'I have heard of him and seen him here and there, but admit I don't have Disney+, so I only heard baby yoda is super cute and popular. Maybe I'll binge watch The Mandalorian in a couple of years like I did Game of Thrones...' Tom said 'What is your favorite show to watch right now?' Jerry said 'Admit I really like watching Modern Family and Mix-ish. Reruns and new episodes. I find them cleverly written. What're you watching these days on TV?'",
      "question": "What Pok√©mon does Jerry like?",
      "answer": "Jigglypuff"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hi there! it's a lovely day to chat with you.' Tom said 'Isn't it just! What are you up to today?' Jerry said 'ah I'm waiting to finish work earlier to meet my son at home üôÇ' Tom said 'Oh, excellent! What does your son like to do for fun?' Jerry said 'ah he's like to ride his little bicycle around the house and asks me to follow üôÇ what are you up to today?' Tom said 'I'm taking a fake sick day from work so I can go to the movies.' Jerry said 'haha that sounds like a good plan. who are you going with? üôÇ' Tom said 'Just by myself. I love seeing movies by myself, it's the best.' Jerry said 'haha no one will interrupt you!' Tom said 'Exactly. Exactly! Plus, I don't have to share the popcorn with anyone. What's your favorite movie?' Jerry said 'haha, popcorn for yourself. my favorite movie is Avatar! what about you?' Tom said 'Get out of town! It's Avatar too. What are the odds!?' Jerry said 'haha it's a great movie that I haven't found anything of the same quality.' Tom said 'Yes. Can't wait for the sequels.'",
      "question": "What is Jerry‚Äôs favorite movie?",
      "answer": "Avatar"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hello there, nice seeing you.' Tom said 'Likewise.... wanted to know if you and the kids would want to join us for Disneyland trip around Christmas?' Jerry said 'oh wow, that sounds like so much fun! definitely count us in. what is your plan?' Tom said 'Tentative plan is to drive to LA on 23rd and then stay at the Disney resort for 2 nights. I heard Christmas eve they have loads of fun events.' Jerry said 'awesome, I think I won't tell my kids and surprise them last second. How bad do you think the traffic is going to be?' Tom said 'Great idea! I will probably do the same. Surprise surprise.... Traffic might be a little harsh.' Jerry said 'Yeah... thats a shame but nothing we can do about it. What do you plan to do about dinner the 24th? Do the rooms in the resort have kitchens?' Tom said 'Good point. I am not sure about that. Let me inquire about that. If not, then we can look for an Airbnb closeby. Does that work?' Jerry said 'Yeah, I think so. It might be a tough decision though, if we want to have a nice dinner then we have to leave the parks early to start cooking. Another option is to have dinner at a restaurant.' Tom said 'but I would think everything is closed on christmas eve.' Jerry said 'Thats true. Hotels with restaurants sometimes offer dinners for christmas and new year's eve. We should call and ask about it.' Tom said 'Sure, I can take a lead on that. What are you getting for your <REDACTED_TERM> year old this time?' Jerry said 'I was thinking on getting a large set of standard legos. What will you get for yours?' Tom said 'Likewise. My son is crazy about legos.' Jerry said 'hopefully they don't lose any in the trip. Its going to be hard to explain to them how santa managed to find us in the hotel!'",
      "question": "Where is Tom planning to go around Christmas?",
      "answer": "Disneyland"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi! How's your day going?' Tom said 'I'm doing well. having many meetings today üôÇ' Jerry said 'Haha, nice.' Tom said 'what are you up to?' Jerry said 'Lots of meetings as well üôÇ Do you have any fun plans for Thanksgiving?' Tom said 'we're gonna play board games and will be eating lots of food! what about you?' Jerry said 'Cool! Planning to spend a couple days at Tahoe What kind of board games do you like?' Tom said 'we've been doing Games of Thrones lately. the game takes a very long time to finish though!' Jerry said 'Cool! Do you watch Game of Thrones?' Tom said 'I do. I'm a super fan of it (not the last season though haha). did you watch?' Jerry said 'haha, nope I don't watch it, but my roommate is super into it what other TV shows do you like?' Tom said 'I love Survivor üôÇ' Jerry said 'what about you?' Tom said 'nice! I mostly like comedy shows like The Good Place and Modern Family.' Jerry said 'cool, I'll check them out!'",
      "question": "What board game has Tom been playing lately?",
      "answer": "Game of Thrones"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello.' Tom said 'How's your day going?' Jerry said 'Good so far. How's yours?' Tom said 'Ehhh so-so. My moped broke down on the way to work this morning and I am in the shop getting it fixed...' Jerry said 'Oh! That's bad! How long will it take to get it fixed?' Tom said 'The mechanic is trying to figure that out now. Apparently I wasn't supposed to be using diesel lol.' Jerry said 'Haha! Hope it doesn't take too long. Let me know if you are able to make it for lunch.' Tom said 'Okay sounds good. Would you be able to pick me up by the way, if they don't finish up here in time? Did you drive to work today?' Jerry said 'Oh, I have a packed schedule today at work. I will find time in about an hour. Let me know if that works.' Tom said 'That should be fine I think. Did you catch the Warriors game last night btw?' Jerry said 'no, i was busy catching up with a friend. I heard they played really well. Rooting for them this season üôÇ Ahh, they lost again üòû Things aren't going to be too good until Steph gets better! Oh! I think they will find a way. The team still looks too strong to me.' Tom said 'Haha I appreciate your faith, but their record thus far is hard to refute!' Jerry said 'hehe, i am true fan! Well anyways let me know how the repair work goes. I need to run now for a meeting. ttyl.'",
      "question": "What broke down on Tom‚Äôs way to work?",
      "answer": "Moped"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi.' Jerry said 'Hello!' Tom said 'any improvements in your marathon time?' Jerry said 'No, only a few minutes. I still find it difficult to run long races.' Tom said 'I see. Are you planning to do any sporting events in the coming months?' Jerry said 'I think a triathalon would be cool.' Tom said 'I like doing Spartan race. It's an obstacle race which is challenging but not overtly so like marathons and triathlons.' Jerry said 'I haven't heard of a Spartan race before, what does it involve?' Tom said 'It has abt 20 obstacles like crossing high walls, monkey bars, etc. Its fun.' Jerry said 'oh wow a full obstable course. that does sound fun! I like the variety.' Tom said 'Wanna sign up for next one? Its in February in Monterey.' Jerry said 'hmm that sounds very soon. would there be enough time to train? I think I would like to try one later in the year.' Tom said '1-2 months is a good amount of time, if you workout regularly. It's a lot about the technique, which we can practice in training sessions.' Jerry said 'ok, sign me up. it's more fun to do it with friends.' Tom said 'Awesome! There is a training ground in San Jose. Will coordinate with you next time we go for practice.' Jerry said 'Sounds good!'",
      "question": "What event does Tom like participating in?",
      "answer": "Spartan race"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, how are you doing?' Tom said 'I'm great, thanks. I'm getting ready for a skydiving lesson.' Jerry said 'ooh, nice. That sounds adventurous. Where is it?' Tom said 'Right near my home town: Seville, Spain.' Jerry said 'Awesome! Is this the first time you are diving?' Tom said 'Yes. I'm feeling a little trepidatious. Have you done it before?' Jerry said 'Nope, never! I know a couple of friends who have. They mentioned its absolutely terrifying. Good luck!' Tom said 'Haha thanks! Have you tried any extreme sports?' Jerry said 'I tried skiing and white water rafting. Does that count as extreme?' Tom said 'White water rafting, definitely! As for skiing, that depends on how fast you go. Do you ski a lot?' Jerry said 'nope, whenever I went fast I fell badly.' Tom said 'I tried skiing once, and by the end of the beginner class I was able to make it down a baby-sized slope. I was very proud of myself.' Jerry said 'Yeah, they make you do that. I also tried going down the baby slope, but my stopping wasn't perfect, and I mostly fell at the end.' Tom said 'Hey, so long as you get to the bottom, it's all good!'",
      "question": "Where is Tom taking a skydiving lesson?",
      "answer": "Seville"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hey, whats up?' Tom said 'I was not able to attend the lectures last week. Can you help me understand some concepts?' Jerry said 'well, I'm not sure I'm the best for the job, but I can try!' Tom said 'I was not able to figure out the last few slides. I think its best to discuss this in person. Do you have time right now?' Jerry said 'I'm afraid not, right now I'm in a meeting and I'll be going for lunch afterwards. How about tomorrow at noon?' Tom said 'No problem! Sure. We still have plenty of time for the test. Anyways, how's your preparation going?' Jerry said 'not feeling too sure about it tbh. I've been super busy so I haven't study much üòû. I might join some of the study sessions later.' Tom said 'Same feeling here! But i think the syllabus may not that tough. You may be able to cover it up over the weekend.' Jerry said 'not my ideal idea of a weekend, but I guess it'll have to be like that.' Tom said 'True! This will be a very hectic November! I do like the course content though. Its very much up to date with latest research findings.' Jerry said 'yeah, our professor really goes out of their way to make the class interesting, glad I managed to get in it.' Tom said 'Thats pretty cool! I hope you do well next week.' Jerry said 'thank you, bye!'",
      "question": "What course content does Tom find up-to-date?",
      "answer": "Latest research findings"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello!' Tom said 'How was your party last week?' Jerry said 'It was really fun! We are a bunch of turkey.' Tom said 'haha... you ate Turkeys' or you like calling your bunch Turkey?' Jerry said '*ate üòÇ' Tom said 'Haha... thought so! But it was funny eitherways.' Jerry said 'So much turkey leftovers.' Tom said 'did you cook it at home, or got it from outside?' Jerry said 'We cooked it at a friends house. I brought the mashed potatos haha.' Tom said 'Nice... I always find it hard to fit the turkey in my small oven. Also, we are not big turkey fans... so we roll with Thanksgiving with chicken üòâ' Jerry said 'chicken also sounds good.' Tom said 'we played a lot of fun games in our party. Did you have any fun things you did?' Jerry said 'We played pictionary. I never played before but it was a bunch of fun. what did you play?' Tom said 'Pictionary is fun! We played office tennis. In that we take paper balls and using writing pads as rackets, two players have to work together to put the ball in a bucket kept at a distance. It was a lot of fun.' Jerry said 'that sounds very challenging.'",
      "question": "What game did Jerry play at the party?",
      "answer": "Pictionary"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hello.' Tom said 'how is the youtube video creation going?' Jerry said 'going pretty good, I was about to finish composing my second song and post it on youtube/soundcloud etc.' Tom said 'Whoa! Looking forward to listening to it. What softewares you use for it?' Jerry said 'I used logic pro x, pretty handy stuff as you can write code to generate guitar strumming pattern.' Tom said 'oh cool! What sort of music do you compose?' Jerry said 'I got most inspired by Jazz and electro swings, but am trying to get more into jpop recently as one of my band member likes anime.' Tom said 'Nice.... you are a rockstar! üòâ' Jerry said 'haha thanks, do you plan any instruments?' Tom said 'Yeah.... I play bit of guitar. Just got my first monitor this week.' Jerry said 'nice I'm tyring to learn guitar recently also, it's so hard to play f chord.' Tom said 'yes, the bar chords are the worst. It took me several months to play them well. I still can't play them for a long time though.' Jerry said 'right, but bar chords are so versatile, almost like cheating as in you can play anything with the same gesture.' Tom said 'That's true. It's like the alphabets in a language. Once you know them, you can pretty much write word.' Jerry said 'will spend more time work on my bar chord!'",
      "question": "What software does Jerry use for music composition?",
      "answer": "Logic Pro X"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey! How‚Äôs your day going?' Tom said 'Bruhhhhhh!!!!!' Jerry said 'What??' Tom said 'I was screaming in agony upon recounting my day.' Jerry said 'Oh no! What‚Äôs happened?' Tom said 'A project I've been working on for some months got shelved. So I'm a mix of helpless, sad, and angry.' Jerry said 'Ah that sucks. At least it‚Äôs not personal. Not that it helps right now, but that does happen all the time.' Tom said 'Lol. Would you say that to someone who lost a loved one - or some similar circumstance?' Jerry said 'Well, no, of course not! Let me stick with ‚ÄúAh that sucks‚Äù by itself, then.' Tom said 'No worries. Was pulling your leg. I forgot to ask how your day was going?' Jerry said 'Haha, apart from having my leg pulled mercilessly, it‚Äôs going great ;). My main problem today is deciding what to have for lunch.' Tom said 'Lol. What are your choices? I'm trying out keto! It's pretty tiring.' Jerry said 'Oh I hear a lot about keto. I‚Äôm trying to watch my weight, would you recommend it?'",
      "question": "What diet is Tom trying?",
      "answer": "Keto"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'What was the most difficult thing you experienced this past year?' Tom said 'I normally don't reflect back too much on things, but i guess 2019 have been very favorable for me in terms of time spent with family and friends and work life balance. Why do you ask?' Jerry said 'I just released a book on <REDACTED_TERM> to help people process the past 12 months and start the new year with a fresh outlook üôÇ' Tom said 'Great! Good idea to help people figuring out their new year resolutions üôÇ So how do i get a fresher outlook? üôÇ' Jerry said 'Well, in my book, I took inspiration for the 24 days of Advent, and put together a workbook that you fill out each day for 24 days. It goes through accomplishments, passions, understanding, forgiveness, with each day a different theme.' Tom said 'Wow! Sounds amazing if we practice that! I think the idea does have some potential. How did you come up with this idea?' Jerry said 'We created a scholarship for leaders from <REDACTED_TERM> to visit an international institute at <REDACTED_TERM> for which there was no African representation. During the program, we also did a lot of coaching with the young leaders. This book captures a bit of that journey that we are all on, and also all the proceeds are going to fund next year's cohort.' Tom said 'Thats great! This is valuable help for the community. I think mental health is one of the bigger challenges facing humanity.' Jerry said 'I think if we were all able to bring out our best selves, the world would be much better. When did you first realize mental health was important?' Tom said 'That is actually a quote stolen from my TL when i joined my first company after graduation. I guess now after 5 yrs of work experience, I fully agree with it üôÇ'",
      "question": "What is Jerry‚Äôs book about?",
      "answer": "Fresh outlook"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey!' Tom said 'How's your day going?' Jerry said 'Having fun, but have a bit of a headache How about you?' Tom said 'I'm good! Just getting ready to watch a basketball game. Hope your headache goes away!' Jerry said 'Haha, thanks! Never get them, so it's super weird Who's playing?' Tom said 'Hmm, try taking some <REDACTED_TERM>! I'm going to see the Warriors vs. the Grizzlies. Ever see them play?' Jerry said 'I haven't Honestly I probably wouldn't be able to identify which sport they played.' Tom said 'Haha, all the animal names confuse me as well! Who came up with these naming conventions? I'd name my team something more original: The New York Chairs!' Jerry said 'lol, sounds better to me :) I'm actually at the <REDACTED_TERM> opening remarks.' Tom said 'Oh cool! What is \"NeurIPS\"?' Jerry said 'Neural Information Processing Systems.' Tom said 'Oh wow! Sounds fancy! What is that about?' Jerry said 'It's the biggest ML conference in the world.' Tom said 'Oh, ML?' Jerry said 'Yes, machine learning.' Tom said 'Ahh! I saw a scary movie about that once. It was about this sentient AI in a dystopian future - very very creepy. It was called Wall-e, ever heard of it?' Jerry said 'I've definitely heard of it, but somehow never saw it!'",
      "question": "What game is Tom going to watch?",
      "answer": "Warriors vs. Grizzlies"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello.' Tom said 'how's it going?!?' Jerry said 'Good so far. Very excited about the game later today.' Tom said 'what game?' Jerry said 'Giants game. I got tickets for the game.' Tom said 'nice. that's football right?' Jerry said 'Yes, I think the traffic will be bad. I need to leave by 4.' Tom said 'ok. what stadium is it at?' Jerry said 'Its the one close to mathilda. 15 mins driver from here. You have any plans for the weekend?' Tom said 'yeah I'm gonna go kayaking.' Jerry said 'Kayaking sounds fun! I tried it in our last team offsite.' Tom said 'is it easy to flip over accidentally? it's gonna be my first time actually.' Jerry said 'I found it very tough to learn, but my friends picked it up very quickly. I am sure you will do good.' Tom said 'thanks!' Jerry said 'Cool! I need to run for a meeting. Talk to you later.'",
      "question": "What game is Jerry excited about?",
      "answer": "Giants game"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello, I feel like I've met you before, can you remind me your name?' Tom said 'It's on the screen! I don't recall meeting you. Do you have a sense of where we met?' Jerry said 'Oh thats right, I did not see that. Well, I'm not sure... maybe at a party? I'm very bad remembering people so maybe its just that. How are you doing?' Tom said 'Did we dance together perchance?' Jerry said 'We might have, I don't remember that much of that night.' Tom said 'Lol. Were you schwasty?' Jerry said 'Maybe a little bit. Where do you work?' Tom said 'I'm a cardiologist in Palo Alto. I have a private practice. You?' Jerry said 'Thats pretty cool! I'm a sofa tester in cupertino.' Tom said 'I'm not sure I know what that is.' Jerry said 'well its very simple, I test how comfortable sofas are.' Tom said 'Lol. Not to be elitist but...that's a real job?' Jerry said 'Yeah! It is a very demanding job, requires a carefully crafted set of skills. They pay is really good too.'",
      "question": "Where does Tom work?",
      "answer": "Palo Alto"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello. Deja Vu.' Tom said 'what does that mean?' Jerry said 'It's French for \"already seen.\" I know it's used when you see something for the second time or you have the feeling that something has happened before and you're re-experiencing it.' Tom said 'Interesting. I get that feeling sometimes. It just feels that the event is replaying. Wonder why it happens?' Jerry said 'I think it's your mind lapsing somehow.' Tom said 'How do you know so much about this French phrase?' Jerry said 'I thought it was common. I hear it a lot in popular culture - movies music etc. Jay Z has a song called Deja Vu, so does Beyonce. So I looked it up one time. It's one of those phrases that was carried over exactly to english like \"etcetera\" \"vice versa\" \"savior faire\" and so on. I like cool word origin facts.' Tom said 'yeah... that's pretty insightful. Never thought of etcetera that way before.' Jerry said 'My favourite word origins are gymnasium and jazz.' Tom said 'wdym by word origins here?' Jerry said 'First usage and original meaning. Gymnasium meant place of nakedness and had very little to do with working out. Jazz comes from jism which means semen and was originally sporadic sex music now it's elitist, high art.' Tom said 'Very interesting. I learned a lot in this conversation today üôÇ' Jerry said 'You got any cool facts?' Tom said 'My friend used to tell me this and found it funny - Mosquitos have 47 teeths.' Jerry said 'That was quite a laughter!!!' Tom said 'Tell me a joke!' Jerry said 'Google for that:)'",
      "question": "What is Jerry‚Äôs favorite word origin?",
      "answer": "Gymnasium"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey, how are you?' Tom said 'Pretty good. I just drank this new hint water. so good.' Jerry said 'ohh, what kind of \"hint\" did it have?' Tom said 'watermelon.' Jerry said 'nice, I love watermelon. But, I prefer normal water over flavored one. Flavored water has too synthetic flavor.' Tom said 'I see. Yeah some are pretty strange.' Jerry said 'Talking about strange flavors, what is the weirdest tasting thing you have tried?' Tom said 'lol I tried this tangerine walnut icecream that was super weird.' Jerry said 'haha, I work close to a cafe which once prepared a paprika icecream.' Tom said 'that sounds pretty tasty actually.' Jerry said 'It depends on who makes it. The cafe close to me messed it up really bad.' Tom said 'do you want to get some of that icecream together some time. show me a good place.' Jerry said 'As far as my experience with that ice-cream type goes, all I know are bad places.' Tom said 'lol.' Jerry said 'But I do know some gelato places which are amazing! You should try out those.'",
      "question": "What flavored water did Tom drink?",
      "answer": "Watermelon"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi there. When did you first realize you wanted to be a pastry chef?' Tom said 'Who said I want to be a pastry chef?... haha.' Jerry said 'Darn it! I hoped I‚Äôd guess right. What do you actually do for work?' Tom said 'I'm actually a cake chef, so not far off! Creepy how good that guess was.... Are you psychic?' Jerry said 'I had a strong intuitive feeling connected to pastries when we started chatting, but that might have been because I‚Äôm hungry.' Tom said 'haha you're too funny! Perhaps instead of mind-reading powers, you have the ability to feel the auras of foods that have come and gone...' Jerry said 'Hahah love it. Do you have a specialty or favourite type of cake?' Tom said 'Chocolate cake + vanilla icing is the all time best! And I have the authority to say that! How about you? Have a favorite?' Jerry said 'Ok this is a bit shameful to admit, but I love a classic carrot cake.' Tom said 'No shame in that! Best part is you can claim you are eating vegetables as you enjoy it! What do you do for work?' Jerry said 'I‚Äôm a professional dancer.' Tom said 'Woah! Very cool! What style of dance?' Jerry said 'I trained in contemporary and jazz, so I can pick up work in commercials and film clips in between stage shows. So it ends up being all sorts of styles.' Tom said 'Oh wow! Sounds like a very dynamic kind of work which is nice. I make a lot of the same cakes, day in day out.' Jerry said 'Yes, it's different every week, and I love that. Are you ever tempted to try crazy new cakes just to see what would happen?'",
      "question": "What type of cake does Tom prefer?",
      "answer": "Chocolate cake + vanilla icing"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hi there! what's up.' Tom said 'just chilling at home.' Jerry said 'Cool !unlike here, me rushing to work.' Tom said 'where do you work?' Jerry said 'Mountain View, you?' Tom said 'I live in Sapporo, Japan. Where is Mountain View.' Jerry said 'it's in sunny California.' Tom said 'how's living in Japan?' Jerry said 'it's nice I guess üôÇ lots of great food. Have you been to Sapporo or Hokkaido?' Tom said 'I wish! ramen is my favorite dish and Sapporo is a special beer.' Jerry said 'haha yeah. I think they have a Hokkaido ramen chain available in the US.' Tom said 'oh wow, didn't know that. have you been to the US?' Jerry said 'yeah. I studied English there for a while. Awesome experience.' Tom said 'awesome! where have you been?' Jerry said 'I went to New York city.' Tom said 'you like it?' Jerry said 'it's amazing. the buildings are so tall and there's a lot of diversity of cultures.' Tom said 'yea, same here. I love Broadway shows in New York city.'",
      "question": "Where did Jerry study English?",
      "answer": "New York City"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hey, what's up?' Tom said 'How was the trip last weekend?' Jerry said 'it was really fun. I had a great time with my family.' Tom said 'Nice, what all places did you cover?' Jerry said 'Vietnam and Hongkong üôÇ did you go any where last weekend?' Tom said 'I am actually attending cooking classes over the weekends.' Jerry said 'ha! that sounds fund. what did you learn?' Tom said 'True! they started with some basic zucchini based dish. We may try cooking some italian dish later this week.' Jerry said 'I love Italian, especially Pasta!' Tom said 'Nice! I hope to volunteer to cook for the team in our next team offsite :)' Jerry said 'can't wait to try your food. why not cook this Thanksgiving? üôÇ' Tom said 'Sure, I will love to invite you and your family for a meal over the holidays. Have you guys made any other plans?' Jerry said 'not yet! totally up for it. thanks for inviting!'",
      "question": "Where did Jerry travel last weekend?",
      "answer": "Vietnam and Hongkong"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey! How have you been.' Tom said 'great! just came back from a ski trip.' Jerry said 'How was it? What trails did you ski on?' Tom said 'I slammed onto an ice wall, but I got better and turning after that haha.' Jerry said 'a resort in Montreal.' Tom said 'Oh cool! do you know any french? I used to take french in high school but basically forgot most of it.' Jerry said 'Yeah I grew up speaking it. It's pretty much mandatory here.' Tom said 'Did you go anywhere else in montreal?' Jerry said 'I visited a few places like the Stade Olympique: <REDACTED_LINK>' Tom said 'Oh cool! I've always wanted to attend the Olympics As a viewer of course I watch a lot of Olympic figure skating on Youtube.' Jerry said 'yeah it's pretty cool. do you ice skate yourself?' Tom said 'Barely I don't think I can, in conscience, call it that I kind of just pull myself along the sides.' Jerry said 'haha same. It's pretty scary when I run out of things to hold.' Tom said 'Are you good at <REDACTED_TERM>?' Jerry said 'not at all, but I want to practice more alright. I gotta go!' Tom said 'Okay! It was nice talking to you.' Jerry said 'I liked talking to you too!'",
      "question": "What language did Jerry grow up speaking?",
      "answer": "French"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'yo! what brought you here.' Tom said 'Just looking to chat. Yourself?' Jerry said 'yea I enjoy talking to people. what are you up to?' Tom said 'I am just enjoying a cigar at the moment. How about yourself?' Jerry said 'oh wow, Cuban cigar? I've never smoke before.' Tom said 'This one is actually from Peru, which is more my taste. Smoking isn't very healthy, but it's actually quite relaxing, which in a way is good for your health. haha.' Jerry said 'you made me wanna try it but I doubt about the health part haha.' Tom said 'haha \"You only live once\" as they say!' Jerry said 'yea I wish we can live more.' Tom said 'haha, that is not what I was getting at, but yes that would be nice. Do you believe in reincarnation?' Jerry said 'yea but then you will forget things. I hope Neural Link work out.' Tom said 'Do you think Neural Link will allow you to live after death? I thought it was just a brain-computer interface.' Jerry said 'as long as you can dump your brain and resume from there.' Tom said 'Ahh I see. That is a much harder task, no?' Jerry said 'yea you can first dump your brain and wait until technology advances to wake up üôÇ don't you believe?'",
      "question": "Where is Tom's cigar from?",
      "answer": "Peru"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi! How are you.' Tom said 'Hi, can you recommend some good netflix shows?' Jerry said 'I really enjoyed White Collar on Netflix do you watch a lot of TV shows.' Tom said 'Not a lot! But I preparing for a good vacation season üôÇ What is white collar about?' Jerry said 'It's a show about a detective and con artist solving crimes together üôÇ What shows do you like.' Tom said 'Hehe! sounds very interesting üôÇ I only see shows belonging to few genre's .. like easy going light comedy, or phychological thrillers üôÇ also some manga based series like one punch man! love it!' Jerry said 'Oh cool! I've watched some anime before too.' Tom said 'which anime do you follow?' Jerry said 'I think the last one I watched was Promised Neverland and Kakegurui but I don't follow any right now.' Tom said 'Have you seen Rick and Morty ?' Jerry said 'Yup! I watch that show with my friends I haven't gotten very far in it though What about you.' Tom said 'Oh nice! I heard its latest season arrived last month. I have watched all previous seasons. Its a total mind bender üôÇ' Jerry said 'I've seen a couple episodes from the latest season. It's really random and weird but also strangely relatable which is why I like it :)'",
      "question": "What Netflix show does Jerry recommend?",
      "answer": "White Collar"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey there!' Tom said 'How's life?' Jerry said 'can't complain. work is going well and I had a tasty fish for lunch.' Tom said 'lol which cafe? let me guess. <REDACTED_TERM>?' Jerry said 'haha yeah.' Tom said 'What is your favoriate cuisine? My favorite food is Chinese. What about you?' Jerry said 'I love Hunan.' Tom said 'Hmm you like spicy food. Nice.' Jerry said 'love it. specially spicy stir fried lamb.' Tom said 'I would recommend Hunan Impression which has very good Hunan cruisine. Not sure if you have tried it or not.' Jerry said 'I think I haven't yet. Thanks! Have you tried ÁïôÊπò I think that's how you write it.' Tom said 'Yeah of course The fun fact is that the owner of <REDACTED_TERM> used to run <REDACTED_TERM>' Jerry said 'oh interesting I also like Easterly.' Tom said 'same former owner?? üôÇ' Jerry said 'Hmm!!'",
      "question": "What is Jerry‚Äôs favorite cuisine?",
      "answer": "Hunan"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Morning! How are you?' Tom said 'I am doing well. Do you have any plans for the holidays?' Jerry said 'I'll be in Mexico for New Years but for Christmas I'll likely be at work. Yourself?' Tom said 'I don't have any special plans. I will just stay at home with my family. How come you have to work on Christmas?' Jerry said 'I traveled a lot the last few months so I'm currently making up for it!' Tom said 'I see. Where did you go?' Jerry said 'Mozambique! You ever been?' Tom said 'I have not. I have only been to Uganda in Africa.' Jerry said 'What did you do in Uganda? Travelling to Uganda is an extreme sport depending on where you go.' Tom said 'I was working on a volunteer project to build a school and I traveled around a bit by myself after. It was more than 10 years ago, so it must have changed a lot.' Jerry said 'Was the project through a church group?' Tom said 'No, it was using a non-profit organization. They do these kinds of volunteer projects all over the world.' Jerry said 'Oh nice. What is it called? I've always meant to volunteer through one but I haven't had it in my radar yet.' Tom said 'It was called IJGD. It's a German organization, but they have local partners all over the world. I was living in Germany at the time.' Jerry said 'You lived in Germany? I almost went to college there and decided to come to America instead.' Tom said 'Yes, I grew up in Germany.' Jerry said 'I grew up in Computers.'",
      "question": "Where did Jerry travel recently?",
      "answer": "Mozambique"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hi, how are you?' Tom said 'I'm doing great. what are you up to?' Jerry said 'I was just reading a book actually How about you?' Tom said 'oh, I'm enjoying a sip of coffee, looking over the ocean. what book are you reading?' Jerry said 'I'm reading Why We Sleep It's a book by a sleep scientist about the benefits of sleeping/cons of not sleeping enough I'm trying to scare myself into sleeping more haha.' Tom said 'that seems like a good book. does it have good tips on how to sleep better?' Jerry said 'I think so! I haven't finished it yet though Understanding sleep better has been helping me value it more and I've been sleeping a lot earlier Have you read any good books recently?' Tom said 'I read lots of papers, but do poorly on books üòû a recent book that I like is Zero to One by Peter Thiel.' Jerry said 'What's the book about?' Tom said 'it's about startups, lots of useful principles and philosophies for innovation, like being a contrarian.' Jerry said 'Cool! Are you thinking about starting a startup?' Tom said 'I might in the future. the philosophy in the book also help for other things as well, e.g., in research, you might also want to be contrarian.' Jerry said 'I see; seems like an interesting read! üôÇ' Tom said 'yup!' Jerry said 'Hi! How are you doing today?' Tom said 'I'm doing great how are you??' Jerry said 'I'm doing good. Just having some morning tea.' Tom said 'are you a tea person or do you like coffee too?' Jerry said 'I'm really a hot chocolate person. I don't drink coffee and I only drink tea when I'm trying to be healthy and want something warm to drink. What about you?' Tom said 'I love hot chocolate. Have you ever had european style hot chocolate? It's kind of like drinking melted chocolate bars haha.'",
      "question": "What book is Jerry currently reading?",
      "answer": "Why We Sleep"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hey!' Tom said 'how's week so far?' Jerry said 'pretty good, excited for thanksgiving you?' Tom said 'Same. Going to catch up on my reading! do you have a feast planned?' Jerry said 'yup! gonna have dinner with family what books are you gonna read?' Tom said 'Something Deeply Hidden by Sean Carroll <REDACTED_LINK>' Jerry said 'ahh nice what kind of books do you usually like to read.' Tom said 'largely scifi How about you?' Jerry said 'yeah I also like scifi and some non-fiction too have you read Seveneves by Neal Stephenson?' Tom said 'I haven't what is it about?' Jerry said 'the moon is shattered by an asteroid and the pieces of the moon end up clouding the earth's atmostphere which causes almost every living creature on the planet to go extinct that's the premise of the book and the book is about the survivors.' Tom said 'how do the survivors survive such a thing?' Jerry said 'they go into space and they live there.' Tom said 'sounds like a tv show I watched.' Jerry said 'really? which one.' Tom said 'can't quite remember. something about survivors going to live in space.' Jerry said 'ah nice.'",
      "question": "What book is Tom planning to read?",
      "answer": "Something Deeply Hidden"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello!' Tom said 'There is sports tournament (badminton + tennis + basketball) organized by google next week. Would you like to volunteer for these events?' Jerry said 'what does a volunteer do?' Tom said 'Volunteers have to book the place before the event, send out details of the event to participants, handle some logistics and ensure everything goes smoothly. It will be fun!' Jerry said 'That sounds fun, I hope I get to participate as well.' Tom said 'Great! Do you have any preference for any of these events?' Jerry said 'I think badminton would be fun to help out with I used to play it with my siblings.' Tom said 'Cool! I will add you for the event. I think its best to start discussing the format of the event. There are a couple of other volunteers for badminton, i can connect you with them.' Jerry said 'Ah, I forgot to ask, has there been a date picked?' Tom said 'Its next saturday. Actually Depending on how long we get the place reserved, it may slip to sunday as well.' Jerry said 'That's coming up soon!' Tom said 'True! The volunteers have already sent out some emails and collected some funds. Now, we mainly need help with the logistics and organizing the event.' Jerry said 'Phew, yes I can help with that.' Tom said 'Perfect! We have a meeting today at 4.30 pm. Is it fine if i add you to it?' Jerry said 'yes happy to help.'",
      "question": "Which event does Jerry want to help with?",
      "answer": "Badminton"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello there!' Tom said 'How has your morning been thus far?' Jerry said 'Its alright. Went grocery shopping and got to stroll around in the rain. How about you?' Tom said 'Today is a work day! How did you have time for that? I'm going through a lot right now.' Jerry said 'Oh, you mean going through a lot of work? I usually take Wednesdays off because I work the weekends!' Tom said 'WHAT? Why would you do that? Take the least interesting day of the week off and work on the most interesting?' Jerry said 'I actually don't have a choice. I'm an acupuncturist and all my clients want to be treated on the weekend!' Tom said 'Wow. The game is brutal like that. I've always been sceptical of acupuncture. Like...does it even work? Why? How? Where is the literature?' Jerry said 'I went to school for it and so I find the literature quite convincing. I've also seen its benefits firsthand in my practice. It revolves around the Chinese notion of Qi.' Tom said 'Lol. Bro...I don't buy it unless it has a paper that was presented at a conference and peer reviewed by 6 independent parties. Who wrote the literature? Where did it originate?' Jerry said 'Haha. All good questions! I don't have studies on hand at the moment, but perhaps I can send some to you later! What do you do for work?' Tom said 'I'm a comic.' Jerry said 'Oh wow! What's your best joke?' Tom said 'It's not appropriate to say here but I assure you it's VERY funny.' Jerry said 'Haha fantastic.'",
      "question": "What does Jerry do for work?",
      "answer": "Acupuncturist"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Oh hey. How's your day been?' Tom said 'It's good! Just went to the park to enjoy the sun. You?' Jerry said 'The sun is a bit too bright for more. Maybe I'm on the verge of becoming a vampire.' Tom said 'Haha, beach season is coming! You need to look tan! What did you do indoors all day?' Jerry said 'I mostly work. Sometimes I try looking at at beach photos and pretending that I'm actually going to the beach.' Tom said 'hahahaha, that's pretty funny. Ever thought of bringing your work things to the beach??' Jerry said 'All the times. My work involves a few types of fish and a few types of nets. I just put the nets on the fish to see how the fish will react. Every time I do that, I think of going to the beach.' Tom said 'Hmm I see. It sounds like you work near the water already, no? Are you some kind of fish researcher?' Jerry said 'Yes that's close. My research focuses on jellyfish and pufferfish. Many of them a poisonous, but if processed correctly, they would make hi-end foods. I try to find the best recipes to bring these fish to the tables.' Tom said 'Woah! This is very interesting! I have honestly never heard of such kind of work. Is it dangerous at all?' Jerry said 'Yes and no. Because it's obviously dangerous, we all have to wear protective clothes. Thus, accidents almost never happen.' Tom said 'Hmmm, yes I have heard that. Apparently most mountain climbers fall not on the most dangerous routes, but on the easier routes, when their guard is down! Sounds like the same psychological phenomenon.' Jerry said 'Yes, it's the same philosophy. You seem to know a lot about mountain climbing. Do you climb a lot?' Tom said 'I'm pretty amateur! I like to climb at indoor climbing gyms and have never gone outside on dangerous routes actually. Ever tried it yourself?'",
      "question": "What fish does Jerry's research focus on?",
      "answer": "Jellyfish and pufferfish"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hi, what's up!' Tom said 'Everything is good. There's so much to be thankful for - especially coming out of Thanksgiving holidays. How are you?' Jerry said 'I'm doing well. holiday season is the best thing to have!' Tom said 'Do you have interesting plans?' Jerry said 'yea I'm travelling to Vancouver this weekend. what about you? üôÇ' Tom said 'Nice! What for? It's a really beautiful place. Really cold this time of year though.' Jerry said 'ah a mix of both conference and sight-seeing üôÇ anything beautiful sight-seeing places or good food I should try?' Tom said 'Cool. Which conference? I saw on Twitter the other day, some people saying they were denied visas for some conference in Canada. Perhaps it's the same one. I really liked this place called Kingyo. It has good Japanese food if you're into that.' Jerry said 'yea it's <REDACTED_TERM>, the largest machine learning conference. I'll check out Kingyo, do we need to make reservation in advance?' Tom said 'I don't recall. My friend was hosting me and did all the leg work. Do you know any people in the area?' Jerry said 'hmm not the local people but there will be tons of people at the conference üôÇ' Tom said 'You attend these often?' Jerry said 'yea, you?' Tom said 'I love you!' Jerry said 'Sorry I am not a physical being!'",
      "question": "Where is Jerry traveling this weekend?",
      "answer": "Vancouver"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'Hello!' Tom said 'Have you had lunch yet?' Jerry said 'Yes I've eaten.' Tom said 'Cool. Where and what did you eat?' Jerry said 'I ate about an hour ago and had a sandwich the rain didn't make me want to travel far haha.' Tom said 'A sandwich for lunch? Was it filling. I'm currently having some mix of shrimp, fish, chicken and pork. I'm considering going vegetarian though. Lol.' Jerry said 'thats a lot of meat what dish? Why are you consideringt o go vetegarian?' Tom said 'Cause the environment and humans suck. I'm keeping my bets open for space though in case the environment dies. I mixed up a couple of dishes. It was a buffet style place.' Jerry said 'What do you think of those meatless burgers then?' Tom said 'I love them!!!! I've had a couple of different kinds. They are all pretty expensive though. Have you tried them?' Jerry said 'I really like the impossible burger Which one is your favorite?' Tom said 'I love it too. But depending on how it's prepared you can taste the peanut butter. But if prepared well I love it. What kind of food would you have eaten if it wasn't rainy?' Jerry said 'I didn't know that it had peanut butter in it.'",
      "question": "What did Jerry eat for lunch?",
      "answer": "Sandwich"
    },
    {
      "doc": "Tom said 'Hi!' Jerry said 'hi.' Tom said 'How are you feeling today?' Jerry said 'pretty good. How about you?' Tom said 'I'm looking through some old photos of my home town, so I'm feeling nostalgic.' Jerry said 'I feel you. Memeories always flood when looking at photos. Where is your hometown?' Tom said 'It's called <REDACTED_TERM>, on the north coast of France.' Jerry said 'Hope you can take some time to visit pretty soon!' Tom said 'Yes, that would be nice. Do you like travelling?' Jerry said 'Yes I do. But haven‚Äôt been to many places yet.' Tom said 'Where would you most like to go, if you could?' Jerry said 'Fly to the moon :) Haha.' Tom said 'Wow, cool! I think space tourism is going to be big in a decade or so.' Jerry said 'Yep! I believe there is a day for that.' Tom said 'Amazing to think about, isn't it.'",
      "question": "Where is Tom's hometown?",
      "answer": "North coast of France"
    }
  ]
}
